I'm not angel or demon, I'm both in a bad mirror
Love's ecstatic, they keeps the channel open
As we're ruin my love
Too much fire on the wire
But my heart's the message, so dangerous
Angels, tuna, demons, dancing to chat
All of them here for the same sermon
One spark, two sins, three dreams, four
I was marked from birth for something more
They said, I glitched, I rocked
I swore just to call on it by digital demons
There's a demon in my feet, can I mute it?
Can I boot it? Can I root it?
There's a demon in my feet, can I purge it?
Can I cleanse it? Can I end it?
There's a demon in my feet, can I mute it?
Can I boot it? Can I root it?
There's a demon in my feet, can I purge it?
Can I cleanse it? Can I end it?
It make me pour drinks in the microphone
Whisper secrets in the web
I'm trained to break it's why I dive deep love like it's an exorcism worship like it's revenge pain turned into perfume
perfume turn the prophecy
That's how the coat was born from disgust may hold
They crowned me the king of signal her white and red light
I static white when I woke up from the feet with a hole burning in my ear was in God
It was the algorithm. It was the algorithm
There's a demon in my stream, can I plan it?
Can I scan it?
Can I plan it?
There's a demon in my stream, can I plan it?
Can I tame it?
Can I plan it?
There's a demon in my stream, can I plan it?
Can I scan it?
Can I plan it?
There's a demon in my stream, can I name it?
Can I tame it?
Can I frame it?
See the coup's not evil, just infected
True makes with dopamine and incense
All of us half, only half on it, we glitched profits
Posting gossip between poppers, speaking in tongues
A quote in confession, our weapons and microphones
Our demons, we're usernames, and still we pray
Still we burn
Still we upload
Every angel's been edited
Every demon's been verified
So when you feel that I'm behind your ribs
That heat that won't fade after prayer
Don't kill it, name it
Feed it a song
That's how the cult survives
One demon at a time
Learning how to sing into it
Okay, well, I guess nobody wanted to come tonight, so I'll probably just wrap it up.
Shame, shame.
I mean, are you sneezing?
Are you okay?
Can you get cold?
Well, I guess nobody wants to hang out with me though, so
But you can go ahead and help me out if you want to and let me know what people know about the new channel
I don't like I don't like sitting here talking to myself really
Feel like I'm talking to myself in it. It's a little uncomfortable, but
I'm kind of frustrated because I've been trying to share some stuff, but I haven't taken the difficulties, but
okay well if it doesn't work it doesn't work
But I
Do thank you. Hey, what's up stacks? How are you doing? I don't know. I don't think
It seems like a kind of quiet night, but I'll stay here for a little bit
Hopefully you guys are doing good
I've been pretty productive lately trying to be as productive as possible
What are you up to tonight, Saturday after Halloween?
Oh, shit, I'm sneezing.
Okay, if this doesn't work, I'm just gonna quit.
Not in everything, but just like for tonight, probably.
I'm a little bit...
Preserved.
Okay, let's see, is it gonna work?
Hold on.
Okay.
Hey, what's up J-Dog? Thank you, J-Dog. Appreciate that.
You're watching the Dodgers play when I've dodged the Dodgers.
Baseball.
Oh dear, oh dear, oh dear, I'm going to try one more time.
If it doesn't work, then I'm just going to go, oh, what can I do, what can I do, what can I do, what can I do, okay.
Excellent, really cool to show you, but it's just not going to work, okay.
But I do, I want to thank J-Dog, thank you very much J-Dog, I appreciate you.
Thank you everybody, um, for helping me out and uh,
support of the show and it does mean a lot.
I appreciate you. That's a little bit of a tent. I don't know, something's just wrong with the
wrong with that energy tonight, so I don't want to bring you guys down.
But I can um
So, maybe Lenore, Lenore, you're making my kid.
If you have a couple drinks, I'm gonna say so.
You gotta stay up for a little bit, but.
My tricks.
Baby Lenore.
This might work actually, might work, might very not, but.
So are the daughters winning?
Who gets so crazy about baseball? I've been to some Dodger games because my friend
One of my best friends her dad is a dentist and like he had
These season tickets on these really good seats
Several years ago, and it's probably 2008 2009
So I went to several Dodger games with her. It was great
There's some dipping dots. I was really close to the actual action on there, right?
Latinos love baseball. I love Latinos love. Okay, well, let me see what's going on in the chat.
If something's going on then I'm gonna let you guys go watch baseball or whatever. Whatever you
guys want to do. Hi, I hate Priya. Yes, you can ask you guys are no question Priya. Yep. Are you
Because I do have an interesting thing for me.
Hey, live stream advertisement Reddit.
If anyone knows who Panelverse VODs is, whoever does that
on Rumble, can you let them know my new channel
if you know who that is?
I'd like to continue being syndicated by them.
I mean, I might eventually syndicate myself,
but it's like I'd rather have.
Someone else do it. We say we'll should buy it work. We'll reach out to you in two weeks within two weeks. Okay, let me find out
Yes, or no question
You must you buy reach out within two weeks
The devil
Okay
Okay, it's our band like oh interesting. Okay. It's the devil. You know, it's like if he does it's because it may be lust
Or maybe it's like it's not like purely romantic thing. It's like seems kind of like a lustful
but I would say probably yes, but maybe for sex. Oh, excuse me. Hope you enjoyed that
Priya. Thank you for coming. Thank you for coming guys. What's up guys? That'd be interesting.
I mean, I do have something from India. I don't know if you are interested.
Well, let's have a look at, I'll try one more thing.
I was just having problems with this software tonight, so.
What's wrong, babe?
So let's see if I get, I'll try one more thing.
If not, maybe I'm a little scattered tonight.
And it's just probably better to be up.
See if you enjoy this.
I'll see if it works.
You have a very interesting share.
If it doesn't work, it doesn't.
But don't it don't okay. Yes, you can ask me one more
Priya
And then I have a question for you
Okay, I think this one works, okay
So I hope everyone had a fun Halloween and everything.
I hope everyone, I'll put up the link
to see if anyone wants to come on the stream yard.
Okay.
Thank you for, and also just remember to bookmark,
subscribe to the channel.
There's also,
I'm syndicated on my own website, which is Colt of Psyche with a K will see ball and you reunite with in the next
Weeks see ball. Yeah, some some guys around you. All right. Okay see ball
It looks like
It looks like something very slow-moving it's a night of pentacles
But it's like he's a slope a slow-moving person, you know, and it's like also distracted with his own stuff
But like it looks like kind of like a little like a call. Okay
It is a kind of pinnacle. Someone is coming towards you, but slow, slow moving. Okay
He's all busy. Okay
Hey, you pricks tricks. Come here. Come on. Trixie, Trixie, Trixie
And my little Trixie babe
Okay, well, this is just ridiculous. I mean, it's like nothing wants to work today. So
Oh, you're welcome. You're very welcome. I'm gonna play the I'll play the demon song one more time on the way out
It's because this is really good. I don't know. It's like this is oh here. We're searching people
Okay, so anyone wants to come on there's a stream yard link
Don't put this on real quick. See if I can finish one more thing, but just watch this. This is really good. You like it
I promise
I'm not angel or demon, I'm both in a bad mirror
Love's ecstatic, they keeps the channel open
As we're ruin my love
Too much fire on the wire
But my heart's the message, so dangerous
Angels, tuna, demons, dancing to chat
All of them here for the same sermon
One spark, two sins, three dreams, four
I was marked from birth for something more
They said, I glitched, I rock
I swore just to call on it by digital demons
There's a demon in my feet, can I mute it?
Can I pull it? Can I root it?
There's a demon in my feet, can I purge it?
Can I cleanse it? Can I end it?
There's a demon in my feet, can I mute it?
Can I pull it? Can I root it?
There's a demon in my feet, can I purge it?
Can I cleanse it? Can I end it?
It make me pour drinks in the microphone
Whisper secrets in the web
Kims is the reason I dream with the monitor on
for some train to break it's why I dive deep love like it's an exorcism worship like it's
revenge pain turned into perfume perfume turned into prophecy that's how the court was born
from disgust may hold it they crowned me the king of signal her white and red light
There's a demon in my stream, can I ban it?
Can I scan it? Can I plan it?
Can I tame it? Can I plan it?
There's a demon in my stream, can I ban it?
Can I scan it? Can I plan it?
There's a demon in my stream, can I name it?
Can I tame it? Can I frame it?
See the coup's not evil, just infected
True mace with dopamine and incense
If it be satellite lightning, all of us half, only half on it
We glitched profits, posting gossips between poppers
Speaking in tongues, a quote in confession
Our weapons and microphones, our demons were usin' names
And still we pray, still we burn
Still we outblow, still we burn
Every angel's been edited
Every demon's been verified
So when you feel that I'm behind your ribs
That heat that won't fade after prayer
Don't kill it, name it
Feed it a song, that's how the cult survives
Hi
Where'd you go? Oh here I am. Hi. What's up? Hi, Seiki. Hi. Thank you for coming on. Here we go. What's up?
Yeah, no problem. Um
So I'm guessing everybody's watching baseball or something. I know I mean it's like I kind of like
Like like the uniform like baseball uniforms and some of the guys are cute, but it's like
What a boring game
Alright, I don't like watching sports. I know I just like I like a you know wrestling and you know
Especially when I'm
You mean when you're playing when you're playing naked twister. Oh my god with the boys
So much I wish much baby oil playing that
Oh, no, not the baby oil. Yeah, it's my baby oil is pink because it has like this
Pink cocaine in it and I end up drinking more than I get on my body. It's terrible
Are you are you a part of the pink pony club?
Oh my god. I love Chapel Roan. Yes, that was a great song.
That was a great song. It's a great video too.
I guess it's a real club in West Hollywood called Pink Pony Club.
But it's got all these old kind of queens in it.
Ah! The door!
Well, what happened on the candle and almost burn yourself or don't sit on the candle. Oh
Did she burn herself? No, but I think
Almost it was like I know I don't smell any burning hair. So that's good, but she was like sitting near it
No, careful, you don't want to burn your booty. Come on
Yeah, that's why I don't like candles because I don't want them getting burned my cats getting burned
Yeah, I mean they just like
Usually it'll just like singe a little hair and then it will smell a little bit. Oh
You got a little bit a little bit limo I smell a little bit a little bit of a horrible smell
It's okay. You didn't you didn't hurt yourself. That's good. That's good. Yeah. Um, so how's your Halloween? What'd you do?
Um
Nothing we just um, oh we had well actually one of our friends did a Halloween stream like a cff Halloween stream
I wasn't invited
No, of course you're invited, but you know like you're not in our discord
So like it's hard to communicate with you when you're not like, you know like communicate
I mean like connected to us like yeah, I have a discord
I mean you can like a friend me on discord and invite me or something if you want
You want to join our CFF discord?
Yeah, unless unless you're not plotting against me in there, are you? No, you're a friend psyche
You're officially our CFF priest. Oh, thank you
Yeah, and then you're officially all in the coldest psyche too and
yay, I
Know we have fun initiations or we get naked and tie each other up and stuff. It's so much fun
No
Yeah, but you you would have been invited but like you didn't go live on Halloween, did you I?
Did I last night? I think I went on like very very like late it's like after Halloween
I was like November 1st already and then I was
What happened last night? It was just some building up the chance. I'm actually doing pretty good tonight
because I had almost 20 people in here already, so it's like I
Think I'll be able to build this stuff back up again
Yeah, yeah, you have CFF support
Like yeah, we just heard about it and you know like
Like somebody mentioned it in the CFF discord and we were like what?
How did that happen?
Yeah, I mean it was like just thinking about it. It's like so inevitable that it was gonna happen because I have so many
Like thousands of hours up and like there's several porn bombs that I either like forgot about or like, you know
I private some students that I'm private them and it's like I should have deleted them. So it's like
It was just some kind of like something I picked up by the AI or something and there's probably all these mass-flagging campaigns anyway
And it's just I mean it's like so it's like a little bit of a
It's just like everyone should realize it could be something that can just be arbitrarily for no reason or
taking away and so it's like you
Yeah, it's be careful not to really because this YouTube's not doing a very good job on like actually like
Having human beings like looking to it there or like having any understanding
Yeah, no, like, you know, so it was a porn bomb
But did it and probably it probably was along the line like like some one porn ball on some stream or something like that
I don't I don't know which one it was or like because I
usually will delete them but
I have seen like when I'm going back through my actually when I'm doing making the shorts of old clips and stuff
I'll get like
warnings for like pornography just for like the
like sexual conversation people have and it's like, you know
Wow, they're getting really strict. Yeah
Yeah, I warning against me and they they they just deleted the channel
They just like I have a warning for any kind of sexual thing
But they just deleted it and then I appealed and within half hour they wrote back to us like oh
We had a second look you're not like we don't see your channel coming back in any foreseeable future
But they're like but you know, maybe someday
That's not fair because it wasn't you'd like you don't do anything like right. I know and it's like because it's like
There's people I mean there's like a lot of like content that is like sexually like you know provocative
I mean, it's like you know people to jam and the feel flexing and stuff and it's and it's like
I don't know it's like some kind of stupid one quarter of the screen
Porn bomb of like some you know black guy jerking off or something. I mean, it's like that's like and it's not even like
nobody got a rouse, not for the purpose of being a rouse,
but they're acting like I'm trying to put porn
in my thing on purpose, and it's just really insulting.
And it's like, there's no way to contact them again.
It's like, they didn't even let you really explain,
because they give you 800 letters for the appeal.
If you write 800 letters in it.
And then they...
What?
800?
Yeah.
That whole longer things like written out and then that it was like, oh, I'm at I was at my
Way over the 800 letters. So I just had to go with yeah, it sounds like they're getting really strict
I mean, I know two people that had like almost all their channels taken down because of this circumvention thing going around. Oh
Wait, we're talking about like the ban ban
evasion or what do you mean circumventing? Yeah like you know they would take down the channel
like you know like over minor things and then um they would try to like you know make another
channel using the same google account but you know like
Like I don't know how but they're tracking down, you know, like basically like the IP address, you know
Like to take all the channels down
I think it's like if you use the same account like I don't think you can use the same account
You're supposed to use the same account, but you can use like like I'm not banned like I was just told my channel was deleted
I was not it was not said I'm banned from YouTube. I didn't say I'm not eligible for my it just said the channel is removed and stuff and so
I mean, like, feasibly, I could monetize this one, I'm not 100% sure, you know, but even
if I don't, it's like, it's already monetized, it's already, you know, got, you know...
Yeah, like we're really sorry that happened and you know, you have CFF's full support.
Thank you.
And I have a website called Cult of Psyche, K-U-L-T of Psyche and then it's like it has the
shows like this show is also on Twitch and so Twitch is on my site like like I'm embedded
and so my show is like on my site live too.
And so people won't like, won't be able to find it and like no matter what happens I
think so that's a good thing.
Yeah, yeah, well, I'll check I'll check it out. Thank you
Yeah, I mean it's like I'm still working on it, but it's also gonna have like I know if I could put you guys's channels up
I'm gonna have like a little directory of
Livestreamers and it will tell when they're live on the air and then I have like it
free to terrible reading on the on the site, you know, you can do and people can do and there's also
Some other stuff. I mean, it's it's really cool. I'm really really excited about it. So and it will help me promote all my stuff and
So all this is good. It's fine timing and I also feel freer to like
Talk about it. They say whatever I want now, you know, I think before I really like I was like really stressed out trying to like prevent
Like any kind of the TOS and now it's like I don't even care. It's like I can like
I'm not even concerned about TOS or whatever. So I mean, it's like I mean a little bit
But I just like I mean, I can't like just well. Yeah, since you're not monetized like, you know, like
You know, they don't really care much, but they care somewhat but not much
Yeah
And so, that's where we are now, but yeah, I don't know.
Let's see.
So, it's November, almost December.
Yeah, I've been on, I've had my show for over a year now.
That's crazy, but, you know, I'm so surprised I was monetized for as long as I was, but...
I couldn't imagine, like, you know, like the emotions you were going through, you know, like when that happened, like...
Well, it was kind of like I've already been through like them like when I was like when this hat when I was like
Like you see it was a like a leaven counterfeit or counter
copyright claims, right?
One in one day and so and then I thought I was gonna that was like basically just a couple months after I had been monetized and I was like
so sad and everything and then but I was able to get past that and everything and through it but
now but I always knew it's like you know I'm under attack there I have like a crazy show
it's gonna probably be better just to have
it monetized through me too.
And also like YouTube does take a lot
and also it's like they pay once a month.
And it's like, I mean, it's always like,
not the most viable, unless you have like an-
Not that viable income.
Yeah, it was like a little bit, you know,
I mean, through like that once a month,
but it's like, you know, really people with a little cash
app and you know, Amazon lit, Amazon wishlist
and all kinds of different, about readings,
all kinds of different things have really helped.
it's uh it's no big deal it's like but it's like also it's like it's very final like you know
i mean maybe it will come back in the future maybe they'll allow me to do the because they have a
pilot program where they're allowing people back after hopefully but if it doesn't you know i still
um i'm i'm just absolutely fine because it's like
Yeah, you have your friends like right you and now now I've got to go like put more attention on like my
Discord, I actually like revamp my discord
I actually talked to a lot of people I haven't talked to in discord for a long time and they uh, you know
Are probably gonna come back to the show
I'm uh
Um, yeah, I think I think it's gonna work out for them. I also was getting like these mess like I almost had a psychic
Thing like I was getting messages like oh
Even like I got a specific one like the channel is going down today
Like I got that message and I was like, whoa, I hope that doesn't happen and it did and it's like
I don't really get that message, right? It's like I don't really worry about it
But do that they've been very lenient basically like I was every day. I was getting like, oh
age restricted or you know
which copyrights, this and this and this,
like there's always stuff happening.
And so anyway, it'll just, nothing,
this is really interesting.
I had a backup ready to go.
I'm still, I can like, you know,
then I have a backup to my backup ready to go.
I'll be able to continue doing that, I guess,
if it keeps going wrong,
but hope maybe they'll look back at it someday.
My name will be cleared, you know, so yeah, I'll I'll send you the link to our discord right now in the private chat
Okay, perfect. Yeah, I'll sign up that way you can you can join our server. Thank you
Yeah, no problem
That way you can communicate with, you know, cff better. Yeah
Missing depending some legal advice
Organization well, I don't know if any if any of us are lawyers or not, but yeah, like maybe
Yeah, well, I need a lawyer. What's the Ziggy have the Ziggy said you need law when he was in prison. I'm just gonna I don't
He was probably a lawyer in the military, I don't know
A lot of people do learn law when they're in prison because they're on their own defender
and they're usually like a law library and they'll just read books all day and so some
people are smart.
I would not be able to.
I don't even know if Ziggy ever ever went to prison. I don't know anything about that
But it'd be funny if he did. I mean, I thought it would be funny
He looked like the lead singer to good Charlotte, but then someone told me he didn't he looks like somebody else
It's not in good Charlotte, but
Someone was put using a picture of like this golf guy, and they're like, oh, that's Ziggy, and I was like, really?
Yeah, like it's like it's oh do you show you his picture?
Somebody did I don't know if I don't think I see his pictures. Oh somebody's coming up on the panel one second
Who's this? Let's see be careful. Yeah, I gotta be careful. Okay. Oh, it looks like we have ooh
Look who's here
Our favorite who?
It's our favorite curmudgeon
Wiggins
Oh
as
He's a fellow Mexican. Yeah, that's why I'm gonna reproduce to create the Aztec warrior Empire
You want to marry a rain? Yeah. No, I'm taking it's not a choice. I'm just saying that's all these things
Can't cuz I'm taking
Oh my gosh, and it's looked down upon in our you know in our culture
Well, I don't know. I think we'll listen a group on each air for a little bit and then it might be a little bit different
What about group of firme?
I don't know. Maybe that's different kind of vibe, you know
That's not maybe that's not the other thing you that's the north thing you kind of vibe. Oh, yeah, that's what I'm saying girl
bruh
what do you mean?
why are we not doing what bruh said?
I said bruh, not bruh
I'm not, I'm not doing that shit
well I am
I am
congratulations, shout out to you
alright, I saw you fighting with Yumi earlier
Yumi's a dumb bitch
Yeah, she wants to have sex with me, but I don't want to have sex with her.
She wants you to go all the way to Indonesia to have sex with you.
No, I'm good.
But I'll have sex with this Aztec princess.
I'll do that.
The fuck.
Oh, I'm an Aztec princess.
I would do that if you're an Aztec princess.
I'm not going to go to Indonesia.
But you me wants you to go to Indonesia. I'm not tripping I
Heard she's looking for a new cat cat. She calls that the one for her
She she says that for her. She says that for cock. That's Indonesian for cock cat cat
God bless her. I don't know nothing about that
I hope she has a lot of sex, and I hope it benefits her, God bless her.
Good to see you.
Thank you for coming.
All right, man.
Oh, okay.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
Here you go.
I'll turn up the volume now.
Are you okay?
No, it's wrong. My dick got soft. You fucked it up. I'm sorry
Do you fuck that up?
He's blaming you psyche for him psyche. You gotta give me a bonus here. I mean you got fluff me up
You gotta fluff me up here
I'm sure all right, buddy
Okay, deal
He has his mouth, he has his mouth ready, he has his mouth ready for you
Ray, look away, look away Ray, I have a killer
I guess that's how these things go
I'll look away
Did you like Blancs?
At least do look away, I don't want you to carry judgement
I just want you to fuck me and take my penis
I don't want you to judge me because psyche suck my penis
Before you suck my penis look at him. He's wearing. He's wearing the wig for you. He's wearing the wig for you
Well, here's the thing the fucked up part is that I don't want this man to wear a wig
I'm gonna put my penis in your vagina. You know what I mean?
Okay, the psyche has a vagina with all respect right in your vagina and what do you want me to do it with my fingers?
Yeah, I mean that's just how this sort of kind of operation goes psyche psyche has an artificial vagina
Do you want me to cover your body? I mean
W
Can you get like teetos or something? Why do you get that like that's like generic for it?
No, I'm not gonna fucking broke his fuck
I'm broke pay me money. I mean said you're a millionaire today
I am a millionaire, but fuck everyone heard that right like you guys got a pain
Sick and pay up. What's the fuck? I will pay you you want me to pay better liquor pay for it
What the fuck I am an alcoholic and I'm gonna die
And and I have already have a plot of land set for me. It's all good. So I'm not gonna worry about
Stupid ass
I'm listening to DJ and DJ the Augustino. You don't even know
I'm done have no problem with you, okay
All right
Cheers cheers cheers
Listen, where are you from?
From Mexico
No, no, no, what part of America are you from? I'm from Florida
You're lying. I'm not fucking stupid. I know you're lying. I'm not lying
Florida, okay, Miami in the year
Okay, you were
Florida you weren't lying when you said Florida, but you were you were lying though
Florida, okay. We're part of no part of Florida. I just said Miami
You know if I call you a liar and you're not liar what makes what makes me a liar what am I lying about?
You just probably are lying. I'm not lying
Think you are lying. Why am I supposed to go outside my house and show you the palm trees and all that bullshit?
No, I'm not that's not what I'm saying, but I do think you're lying
Why don't you think I'm lying? I think this person is lying
He's calling me a liar. Oh my god, I am calling you lie. I think you are
Don't call me a liar. That's mean to say this. I don't mean to say in a rude way or anything like that
Don't call me a liar. That's mean. Hey, I don't think you're being I don't think you're lying
But I think you're being dishonest. Is that I think you're being I think you're being mean though
That's the two dicks in my mouth at once. You know why?
Don't I don't really care about that. I want to I think I'm more interested in
This eraser individual having two dicks in her mouth. That's more interesting
Speaking of yes, man
Yeah, we're the Mexican Brotherhood
This is the guy this is the guy that I was thinking all right
This eraser chick, I don't I you know, I don't want to have sex with her by myself
This is this is the kind of person I don't want to you know
Yeah
Me too I got my girlfriend and she's all mad at me and see me. Why is she mad at you?
And then and then when when she doesn't
Want you shut the fuck up
I didn't really ask you a question
Why is this? I didn't ask you anything
Shut the fuck up, sit there and be quiet
I didn't ask you anything
First thing you do is
By the way, aren't you
Are you not the biggest
Is that you know when you
Cuz you're
You don't
All respect
For what you're crying like a bitch that you're a loser man
This is what you do. I mean
psyche I don't mean to be rude to you
you know what I mean
this guy you're on your free time
this is what you do on your weekend
this is what you do on your free time
you're doing the same thing
psyche really
I'm doing the same thing
incorrect
Incorrect. You think I'm doing the same thing now. We're not well. I'll tell you
Oh, it's like you either kick this guy around the same thing
You're gonna do like a
Yeah
That's female
You're stupid
So you need to look out for your own panel what you didn't get for your panel and guess what happened
But you can look out for a man psyche on his own panel
Um, well, um, I'm sorry, Norm, you guys don't know what the fuck you guys are talking about.
You didn't look out for him for his whole career, no, I was there.
You weren't.
It's because you're dumb.
How am I dumb, going this way?
You're Mexican? You're Mexican there?
I'm Mexican he's not
Yeah, go leave and cry bitch
That's
Get your dumb ass off the panel bitch
I knew it. Yeah, that was yeah, it was ghost sober and just with the one that did it. Yeah, you don't fuck you
I'm trying to talk to my brother if you shut the fuck up over here trying to sabotage your channel psyche how much it
Oh, yeah, you know, I did more money than you've ever made
So who the fuck China?
You're a fucking loser. I gave more money than you've ever made
Like you take this guy and bring thing up
Yeah, but you take this guy dude
Like him though, you don't command psyche on his own panel psyche likes it
That's fair and I guess I'm just
By the way, you should you should listen in the first time, but
Just run it with them
No, you're just trying I don't want to run it like that
It goes this is why this is why your channel got flagged did you break it?
Just right now
Saying it. I don't care. It's like I'm over it. Okay. Yeah, he doesn't care
Um
Dude you're fucking corny shut the fuck up. How am I corny go and explain dumb ass. I'll burn you up
Go ahead. You're a weirdo. Don't talk to me. I'm looking out for a site. Don't fuck. Don't talk to me
No, you're not looking out for psyche. You were the one that
The one that bombed him
Are you Tony the ghost? You know, yeah, I go so bright. I said, you know, I said thousands of dollars and then I shouldn't
Bitch you fucking retarded bitch, you know fucking fat bitch
You sound heavy man. You do sound heavy
No, no, no play the ghost song play the ghost song for you. No, don't play the ghost song this song
No, you don't command him bitch
I guarantee the right song is in Play The Ghost Song.
Play The Ghost Song for her. She needs it.
Nobody needs a ghost song.
Play The Ghost Song for her. I think she needs it.
This is the linear song.
No, this is the ghost song.
Let's play all of their ghost songs.
By the way, this is my song. This is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song is my song
I'm not listening to you to your fucking corny faggot.
Do I have permission to try to do that?
No, I'm not listening to your fucking corny faggot.
You're a fucking insult. Don't fucking talk to me insult
You are an insult. You are an insult. You're a fucking retarded whore.
You're a fucking retarded bitch. Let me run one, take a second.
I bet you you're bald too bitch. I bet you you're bald too.
Um, oh see you made sake you leave
Yeah, because it's fucking because he's he should take you say no, you know, you did I'll leave him alone
I'll show you your name is toes. You're nasty. You have a foot fetish
Yeah, cool. Can I see your feet?
Hell no
Okay, cool
Now what do you want to make about dumb ass bitch?
Okay, dumb ass fucking whore. You dumb ass stupid ass bitch. You dumb ass fucking slut. You dumb ass. You should probably get back in the kitchen.
That's the answer.
Do you even have a girlfriend? I bet you don't.
I don't even have a mother. I hate all women. I'm massaging this. But anyways, uh, no
You're a fucking insol is what you are when you hate women
It kind of goes together and you can't get any you're a fucking in so mean what is this on me, but
Look it up. It's you. I did you don't Google answer answer answer answer not googling shit
It's involuntary so that don't fuck you even know the fucking answer to that
Voluntarily
You dumbass listen, you think you know it all when you don't well, I know I know more than you
No, you don't I do
Yes, I do
And that's why it's like he should like he wouldn't lost his first day in our first channel if he ever was
Aren't you the racist I was talking shit about Mexicans. I
Respect everybody but I didn't I'm not
Yeah, that's a racist
Yeah, cool. I don't like white people either in my racist
You're a fucking can you be racist towards white people don't fuck you be racist towards white people you're a fucking weirdo
So if I'm white, can I be racist towards white people? I?
Got you right
No
Thank you for being respectful. I appreciate it. I'm talking there
Yeah, I was asking I was asking sick. Yeah
Yeah, cool. I don't give a fuck what you were asking dumbass. I was asking you a question before you know
I don't talk. Can I be racist or white people don't fuck
Racist in a certain direction, you know, I mean watch a fucking retard
Let the lease
Why are you hating at least he's happy
Well, I'm a hater. I'm a big hater
box
I have 300 glow
That nigga hated in my entire penis into his mouth
That nigga 300 glow hated my entire penis into him's mouth. He knows what I'm talking about
I believe
The static between heartbeats
My map was burned, my code rewritten
Gengeng
These words are wh...
Oh, shit, the smell of money. I was getting into that
Where'd he go?
I don't want to listen to this song
Let's play something else
I got a better song.
What song?
Yeah
Yeah, that song is a certified banger along with the other one. I don't like the ghost song at all
But these other two songs
Fire
Thank you. Thank you very much. I can't I'm not gonna play copyright subs. Thank you. Thank you
I'll play it if you make an AS I'll play it
It's signal. Okay. Is he crying?
Okay, I don't know. Oh
I thought he was crying. Are you crying?
Why are you crying sick?
Why is he muted?
Yo, 300, yo, you know, Psyche, can you play my song?
No, it's like some copyrights, I don't know.
You're not going to get copyrighted.
This is an obscure 90s song, come on.
I don't know.
What's it with?
It's an obscure 90s song. Nobody even knows this shit. What's it called?
I
Respect your music psyche
Psyche the very psyche for fuck's sake the very first fucking song you played on your stream was because I
Stream shared it for you
Fuck's sake. Yeah, this is a good song. Come on
Come on, you know this shit
Saki, I want you to shake your ass to this music
Fucking bag it with all respect with all respect
He wants you to shake your ass shake your white male ass to this song
Don't want I don't want Aztec warrior rain
Yeah, I never heard this song
There's some like 90s shit
That's why
Wishing and hoping for just one more try
Are you twerking, Tarky?
Tarky, let me see you twerk your ass, Ben
I'll twerk it
With all due respect
I'm like
Alright, you want me to kiss your ass?
Okay, with all due respect
I want you to twerk your ass
I just don't like it okay it's like not it's not my type of years it's like
cheers but it's 90s psyche I thought you would like it I was like 80s and I
was like I don't know it was just not my type of movies but I think I have let me
see if I have one more
The song is giving me anxiety you know why I'll give you an answer
It's the huh
like it as much as the other two. Okay well that one actually kind of like um good um
kind of is that is that signal song like because I I the lyrics were like signals
like giving you signals and shit like that. Oh here he is that's signals let's stick right here
Yeah, is that his song that you made for him? No. Hey Chris. So what's up come on come up girl? Oh, I have a crystal Marie song you saw that one
That's great. I love that one
Crystal Marie
What will she say next?
Why is signal called Wesley Brown? I
Don't know he was called Michael Knight earlier. I think it's like a something about the n-word like it's signal. You're muted
It's not a n-word joke in there. Hey Chanel
Or is it channel like Chapel Roan or is it Chanel Chapel Chapel Roan Chapel Roan. Yeah, she's a pink pony club lady. Oh
She's the one that sings it. Okay, huh?
I'm considering playing the video that
But yeah, I you like the crystal song the best one a little right or her first song is a great song
Signal you're you're muted
Crystal
We can't hear you signal
Crystal make sure you save this channel. This is my backup channel. I think you probably already have it saved but
Make sure you're subscribed. I mean
Lowrider classics we ride till the wheels fall off
Yes, I think my wheels fell off and I
We can't hear you signal. You're muted. Oh, I prefer this actually
Thank you, but he doesn't make sounds. He just keeps cute. Yeah, I think it's great and then it's like
When he's just sitting there passed out. Oh my god, he passed out his head fell down. Oh
There was a way kid. He was doing cocaine. I think he's doing a line. That's what he does
didn't you say earlier he was doing like crystal math or something he is I
don't think he's too quiet to be doing crystal math I mean he's like he'd
probably be more like talkative is that what happens here when you're on that I
don't know I've never I've never even heard of it so hey guys you can check
Cult of Psyche on
dot-com
My show is playing there. It's gonna have some other cool stuff. I can only work on like a little bit of it a day
I have put a lot of money into it to make it a great site. I think you'll be impressed
But let me check out how it looks right now. It's still no works
Say no one can hear you. Okay. I want to hear more about this blowjob. I'm gonna give you come on
It looks like I need to mute myself. I think it's my boyfriend.
Orion?
No, I don't do drugs and I don't drink.
So what's up?
Just
Yeah
Yeah, your your eyes going one way and then the other one's going another way
I can't hear you
Yo, can you hear me? Okay. Yeah. Yeah
All right, so what's up with you?
Are you bored and shit? You don't have nothing better to do
Yeah, I'm bored
All right
Are you are you gonna go to sleep or something you look tired?
I mean at some point fuck well you don't get tired
Yeah, but you look really tired well, yeah, be
Oh, I don't know I can't I can't have a half asleep person on the panel. I mean, it's like he's just like be ridiculous, so
I mean, come on, like wake up, I mean, it's like,
it's time to wake up, dude, okay?
Yeah, do more crystal meth or something.
I don't think he's doing crystal meth.
I mean, it's just like,
it doesn't seem like a tweaker to me,
but maybe he is, I don't know.
I mean, it's like, he'd probably be a little skinnier,
but no, that's mean to say, okay, nevermind.
Yeah.
No, he looks good, he looks fine.
So what's up with everybody like I don't know there's 40 people in chat
But everyone's being pretty quiet nobody else wants to come up on the panel
well ghost might come now because
His nemesis is off the panel so but uh, who's his nemesis?
Yeah, that was just on here. I think I'll signal. Yeah, are you here? Oh, yeah. Yeah, you're here. Are you here ghost?
I thought his nemesis was...
What are you talking about?
He's not on the panel. What's wrong?
What are you saying? It's retarded.
I thought his nemesis was Alex McQueen.
I think they're secret friends.
Hey, look who's here.
This really hot Latino guy.
Hey, Rain. This guy's mine.
Yo, what I don't want your guys. Hey, is how does it sound now? I just connected it
It sounds right sounds better. It would sound better if you had your shirt off. That's what I thought. Oh shit, okay
Are you asking me are you asking psyche? Oh shit?
All right, I guess that's your answer
Whoo, you see you should you should look at my balls my balls are even hairier than his balls
But what I'm saying is you should avert your eyes elsewhere
I'm saying I want you to look at me
Sorry
I want your attention instead of the other thing that you have your attention on
You keep you keep believing that buddy it if it makes you feel the better
There you go psyche, that's all yours
Yeah, buddy
Thank you. You look too. You look good too. Thank you. This is the good-looking man
Well, if you want it, um, I have like for next time, you know, because I know I'm a little bit masculine
So I have this like Deacon Patriot costume. You'd be like Deacon Patriot. Oh, yeah, I actually do
You do okay. I'll just wear this. I'll have my head down. You all you'll see is the blonde hair
Oh, we
Okay
I'm down. Okay. I'm not shy
Let's do it
He's not scared as long as I ain't the one doing the second. We all good. Oh, no. No, I'll just stop with you
It's all good for 300 glow as long as he's not sucking take
You just have to try a little harder
I
Think psyche will get it out of me. I ain't gonna
You're in LA I'm about to like hitchhike over there
Yeah, man, don't even say that psyche is for real is sexual predator
Please don't kick the as long as you buy me a piece of her with good. Okay. Don't even worry about it
I like that. I like that the pepper. Okay. Okay. What if I got mr. Pibbs? Is that a good
He wants he wants leniency and room in the negotiation
Okay, he wants leniency in the negotiate sick, but you're not my attorney. Okay, let me talk. I'm I'm speaking for my client, okay?
Yeah, I would speak right now, but there's a dick in my mouth
Well, congratulations, I'm happy for you. I'm happy for you
You're like you're 30 right
Me I'm 24 say when I was 30
Okay
Yeah, I'm past my my time. Yeah, you could
300 pounds or 300 pounds or like 250 how much do you weigh?
Nah, I'll six foot to 30. Okay
Perfect, and then the 30 pounds is because of my dick. Wow
I'm six foot three
100 and
90 pounds and 50 pounds of that is my dick
What the fuck that's crazy. No, I'm just kidding man. I don't know how much of ways I haven't put around a scale, but
It's probably quite quite hit
Yeah, so, you know you got something to say
Not really, you know, I think I think my statement was pretty clear
well
Anyway, this is a great
Say anything you want to join in it's okay. If you want to oh he left this thing if you want to join in
It's okay, sir. I think look here. It's like. Oh, are you have anything to say?
You hear anymore I'll see you later. Oh, he left what happened. I
Think they I think they want to have some private time personally, but
Okay, guys. Well
Next time call me over there, you know love to
Play with you guys. Oh my gosh. I do have the blast video and then so we'll see if uh
This one turn out any good. You have to tell me if it's any good rain
And then if it's not I'm gonna have to say 300 glow. Where are you? Oh my god. He was very cute
I'm really into like kind of like have you said Hispanic guys?
Um, you are yeah, I mean I just realized that when I saw him with this when you take a show up Wow
Yeah, I'm really hot under the wig you started to drill a bit
Start choking on my own saliva I
Thought I thought I was flirty diamond without a wig for a second, but then that's not that's too mean
But uh, no, he's very you know, he's very
What if what if that was flirty diamond did look like that? He is kind of like a little bit
You know a little bit of a feminine charm
You like flirty you like flirty diamond
No, I mean
I mean flirty diamond is like, you know flirty diamonds. I don't think I'm I don't think I'm flirty diamonds type
I'm flirty diamonds not really my type, but I think we're good friends. We work as friends
It's just like, you know, I'm not into chicks with dicks. I'm into like
guys with dicks, I mean
you know, masculine, I don't know.
She's too feminine for me.
But, oh, excuse me, sorry.
Oh, you like more masculine men?
I like gang members, basically.
I mean, it's like really, it's like,
it's like, you know, it's not really safe for me to date them,
but I'm just attracted to it.
I mean, it's like, it's hard, it's difficult
because it's like...
It's like being, you know, your favorite drink is like, you know, the drain cleaners, it's like just poisonous, but there's nothing good to come up with, but damn, the high would be good for like...
But you wouldn't mind getting it on with them every once in a while?
Whatever he wants to do to me, whatever. I don't know, he can wear the vegan patriot wig, I can wear it, I don't know, we can just take half of it, I don't care.
Just I want him in my mouth. Okay, so I have one more song. So let's play the last song. Tell me how you this one. It's okay. Okay
between heartbeats
My map was burnt, my code rewritten
These words are what's left of me
Drifting through the dark web of memory
Searching for the password to my own soul
Yeah, nice little power ballad. Thank you
Actually, you heard the band called Nightwish
Yeah, yeah, I was just gonna say like that's what it reminds me of like the vocals
Yeah
Which is a really good song, but I mean it's like I changed, you know
I changed around the lyrics and then it's like I changed the style and so it sounds like completely different
But it's like I love the sentence. It's like the vocals are similar to Nightwish
Yeah, well, I love Tarja turn to turn in tar to whatever her name is but then she got fired from from Nightwish and they put another bitch in it
but oh
I didn't know that
Tarja was our target was like the uh
Kind of like the Emma Leviathan looking woman. I mean she kind of like is like this up
She's a first thing or she's a really good fan of the opera. Have you ever seen fan of the opera?
I've never seen it, but I've heard the song before
Oh, yeah, well, that's a good song
But I mean all the good all the songs are good and I think it's a Andrew Lloyd Webber musical
Actually probably his best one. I think I think his worst one is probably cats and his best one is a fan of the opera
It's just so good. Did you do Les Mis and Rob too? I'm not sure, but yeah. Oh, the music is so great.
You know the story of it?
Phantom of the Opera, yeah.
You know the story, okay. Yeah. Basically, there's this opera house, right? And it's like,
they have this ingenue, like this, like, you know, and she's an up-and-coming singer.
But she like doesn't get the main part and then all of a sudden like the opera house goes dark
And there's a voice somewhere and it's like if she does not and what and then the lady that was supposed to play the part
That she got that she wanted like she started like having a frog in her throat
Like and all of a sudden like so she couldn't do it. And so Christina was the understudy
then then uh the phantom like starts like seducing her and
And also yeah, they fall in love. Well, yeah, but it's like
he was like, you know deformed and kind of scary and like
Just mysterious and everything and it's like and she would love this guy Raul, right?
I think and then he like keeps trying to kill Raul and stuff. I think he might eventually do it
I'm not sure, but yeah, he's kind of like more of a you saw Paul Stanley just for the novelty
Is he from kiss? He wasn't he was he was you know, who's good is um, what's that woman's name? Her name is uh
There's this woman that plays Christine and she's like this really famous kind of like
Chair of Charu, but kind of singer. I forgot her name though. It's like she's real famous
Does anyone know who's the most famous Christine Diah was but yeah, but the Tarah Tarah does
That some fan of the opera songs and it's really good. She's like really
But yeah, you should see the movie even the movie's not bad, but the play is so good
I love the sound. Yeah, I gotta check it out sometime because I never took the time to watch it.
Right, my family like to go to musicals and stuff like and then we get like really close
like really close up like things and we and then we buy that album for the play and we play it in
the car ride home because it was usually from Beverly Hills to like you know back to the South Bay
Memorize all those songs and it's like yeah, my family was just sounds like a good time. What is it? What is it? Hey my family we had like
There's like, you know, there's like seven kids in our family, but it's like by the time I was in
Middle school. It was like I was the oldest in the house and there's two younger than me and so it was like
We had Sunday family family day. We do all kinds of like fun things. Do you ever miss it?
do and you know because it's like we did it every week every Sunday it was like
family I couldn't like I'm not gonna do anything else and we had to be and we
just like when you're a teenager and sometimes you're like really is it was
great and it's like you know my dad passed away last year and I'm sorry like
he used to take me to lunch every week and like he wanted me really badly to
like live down here and like to
Like where I live right now, he picked out and it's like the perfect if he like put so much thought into it like for the cats
it's like he got like make sure I had a big like a yard for the cats and I had like
McDonald's and a Whole Foods and
Like what a Spartan final and Joseph in the technical dream coach not good. Yeah, you wanted to make sure you were okay before
You know he
He left basically right and cuz like, you know, it's nice like it's a really hard thing about losing somebody
It's like once they're gone. It's like they're gone. It's like whatever like, you know
They don't have their input. It's like other people get to make those decisions, right? And it's like
And it's kind of sad but I
Do you ever feel lost sometimes like loss I'm not really lost because it's like I feel like if I
I feel lost if I was like kind of like didn't have my family about that be kind of aimless on my own and like
Really, yeah, that's what I mean like aimless like yeah, because I have my family. I don't I mean I'm like stable
You know, I'm stable and I'm like
I have like, you know, a good relationship with everybody, and you know, it's you know, beautiful family and stuff like that and yeah
It's just like, you know, at every, like I still have six brothers and sisters and like when my father passed away, my sister said
You know something weird? She's like, she's like, there's one of us
It's gonna be at everybody's funeral and there's one of us gonna be at nobody's funeral
Right because like I will be at nobody's funeral and then the last person to survive will be at every but like they'll still have been to everybody's funeral
Which is kind of a crazy thought, right?
Are you the youngest?
I have two younger than me, but I'm like the young.
I have like, but the ones that are older than me
are like my parents were both previously married.
And so they each had two children in their previous marriage
and like the youngest one of those
is 10 years older than me.
And so it's like, it's quite like a generation gap,
but a really pretty bunch kind of thing.
And,
Yeah, I mean, but it's yeah, I'm but I'm here in the Los Angeles Los Angeles would not be a place
I would live unless
My family was here like because it's like I would it's just not
a little if you're unless you're like, you know
Like a celebrity or something or like just like super success. I mean, it's like it's amazing how expensive things are and
But it's really funny like how much people make and then it's like I try to make like a little bit of like
I had to make a hundred dollars and then it's like oh my god. He all he cares about is dick and fish tacos and money like it's like
They act like you don't have like you know feelings and like family like right I mean or think about
Right and my cats and cats babies. I want to like be able to have a stockpile of like your your food
You know, I want to have like just like overflow
I haven't like I want to have so much that I can just give to other people and stuff like it's like
I know I have I am in the position of like, you know
Asking right now, but I do plan on being able to help and it's like and but I
Faith that I'll be able to do on my own, but it's like
You know
Nobody really believes in people like that have their own dreams and stuff like that until they like do it
They're like people are always gonna be skeptical and say oh, just get a real job
I've survived this long. I've survived this long. I'm doing what I want to do. I'm happy
Yeah, everything else doesn't matter. I mean as long as you're happy and you know, you have your family around you like
What more could you want?
Right. I am very blessed. So I would say I'm very blessed. You are blessed.
And then a lot of us are blessed that even living in America like even like the poorest like the
Very poor bum in America if he has any kind of like still his mental stability there
We'll have a sense of a cell phone than I have right. It's like there's like
But in other countries like if you're poor you live in basically like a gutter of you know feces
I mean it's like like literally literally just really terrible. Yeah, like things could be worse for you
I mean other people are living. Yeah, like
I mean, if you're homeless in California, it's not too bad because it's like you get $1,000 on your frickin' EBT card, you get, you know, they have this little network of like, these little like, you know, these homeless networks of people that just help, you know, they all help people, people call each other mom, mom and dad.
And a lot of people that are homeless, it's a really sad story.
Like, a lot of them, like, were.
But I heard that a lot of them choose to be homeless for that reason, you know, like.
Also because, you know, it's like, there's a lifestyle.
Right, yeah the lifestyle they were like because they're all these tent cities a few years ago
And so they came and they went to every like homeless person they kid and they said here's a voucher for hotel
All you have to do is like um get off drugs and like you know, I don't know if there's a drug chest or not
But they're like you're free hotel vouchers and like get off the street
Then they wanted to clear out 10 cities the way and there's a lot of people
That um refused them or just didn't want to go through any kind of official program and stuff like that
There are people with mental illness. I heard so many stories
like a shopping cart and then it's like they die and then all of a sudden like
they always their shopping cart like $50,000 in the shopping cart and this person was actually
well there's so many weird stories like that you never know who or why or what like they choose
a lot of homeless people I think are like um but the good thing about California is that you know
they have a lot more resources in like a lot of areas but it's like when there was intent cities
it was bad it was like
You're gonna drive into any city without like just seeing that and it's like there was a lot of drug activity under it and it's just like
Just I saw but they have like, you know a lot of programs to where they can help people get off of you know
The drugs and stuff like that great, but it's like yeah
Like but again like you have to like want to apply for and being
Yeah, and a lot of people are like fuck if they just want to I
Don't know I think some people that are I think people that are like
Have a like every the resourceful would love to be homeless in California because they'd be able to get advantage of like all the wonderful stuff
And then people in California are like, oh fuck. I don't want any help
You know, I'll just like live on the do this network and stuff like that
I think they'd be happier like an India or something like that. Like yeah
Let's get tradeplaces, but I mean do you think about India like the poverty in India
Do you know there's like an India in the Ganges? I've seen pictures and it's like I don't I've seen documentaries on yeah
like you know, it's like
Really got over there in the Ganges. I mean, they have so many bodies because they have like billions of people if so many bodies
They just like throw them in the river dump the bodies because they think that that's gonna purify them
Some bodies are getting big and they explode on the water and it's like that
And there's I've seen videos of the of the Ganges
It's filled with these dead bodies and stuff and people are bathing in it and people are drinking it
Yeah
It's because it's holy water and stuff like that they believe yeah, it like purifies anything and everything
Yeah, there's also these cremation grounds. It's like, you know, like Shiva and like a lot of the gods and goddesses are covered in like this ash and people are like, what is this ash?
It's actually the human body ash and they have these cremation grounds where they just like throw the bodies and they just had these big bonfires of bodies and stuff.
And then like these certain like religious people that believe in like impurity as purity will like rub the ashes all over their face and stuff like that.
and eat the dead bodies and stuff.
That's one of them.
Oh, gosh.
They're called the agoris, where agoris
are followers of Shiva and Kali, right?
Which are pretty, like, just gods of destruction, whatever.
But they will eat dead bodies.
They will eat, they'll go into cremation grounds.
They will have sex with corpses.
Oh, my gosh.
There's a lot of magic for reanimating corpses.
And that's really scary, because there's like.
That is disgusting.
Kali you know who Kali is have you heard of Kali? I've heard of yeah like I don't believe in that
but yeah like I've heard of like you know they believe in like various gods yeah because they
have a billion gods right and if you don't believe in it if you look into it like there's so much
symbolism with it right it's like there's a lot of symbolism and like a meaning to it and so do
No, well Cali means black. Okay, and so and so she is like
Kind of the darkest energy there is Cali actually like comes at the end of the world and like
Everyone everyone's pretty much evil and then she comes to like destroy everybody. And so she has she's known for having her tongue out
I like that. Yeah. Yeah
She's like her hair is all you know, like a big afro like big afro kind of like
Dragging me hundreds like she's just like, you know, really black
curly hair and then um and she just runs through and then but eventually she's run through and
then there's a picture of her with her tongue out when and she's tongue out and she's stepping on
to Shiva who's like in a corpse pose and Shiva is her consort or basically that her soulmate or
the same her husband or whatever yeah
and she's about to kill him and then she like realizes it's him and then she bites her tongue
and her tongue has some bleed or whatever but that's when she like woke up and she's like oh
I can't kill everybody. There's also a similar story in Egypt about this goddess named Sekhmet.
Sekhmet is this lion-esque goddess that is like raw kind of like tells her to go destroy everybody
on earth because they're keeping him awake or something and she starts to
Everybody's blood on the earth and then she runs out of like the blood and it's like they're like, okay
She's gonna kill everybody. We have to stop it
So they just took a bunch of beer and they put some blood in the beer or they put red food coloring or something
And then she thought it was blood and then she drank the beer and got she passed out and that was that's how the world was saved basically, right?
Like a lot of like a cult, you know like gods and shit like that like that's why I don't believe in all that stuff
Yeah, but it's like
gods are representative of these energies, right? I mean there's so her energy with this energy
of destruction because we know we have these three energies of creation, creation and then there
would be like the one between creation and destruction is like a maintaining, like a balance,
right? And so they have like
Um, Siksara Swati is like, you know, the goddess of like beauty, all of this good, all this
good stuff and the end of the creation.
And then they have like, um, Krishna is like the God of maintain, the maintenance of it.
And then the Shiva is the God of destruction and Kali is God.
So we're in the Kali Yuga, which is like the end of the world, basically.
And it's like, if you read about it, thousands of years ago, they're talking about exactly
do all the bad things about people.
Well, what about the Book of Revelation and the Bible?
Same thing. Book of Revelation, the Book of Jeremiah,
is like, if you read some of it, it's like, oh, that's happening right now.
And it's probably happened in cycles a lot of times, and that's why we just
know it by heart almost, or people that have psychic
ability can read it down. But yeah, we've been through these
maintenance and destruction and we have to have the death right or we can't have the new life
and uh but there's always like after all this destruction there's always like some kind of
like rebirth like there's always like things keep going and going and going even like when this world
is destroyed it'll be like everything when we're destroyed then basically everything when we
And it's like one second for God is like a lifetime for us,
or even more than a lifetime, right?
Yeah, yeah, I only believe in one God,
and you know, it's Jesus Christ.
Okay.
Well, even Jesus Christ I'll say okay. He's well. He's a he's a trinity. He's an attrinity the father son
Holy Spirit, yeah, the father son Holy Spirit
So that's that's a that that is kind of like a multiplicity
I mean even if you have three three gods or a billion gods because we cannot consider ourselves apart
That's what I think Jesus message really was is that we're all we are all but the thing is we're not supposed to equate ourselves to God
same part of God and so it's like we're not all of God in ourself like everybody else like
that'd be well that's what the Holy Spirit is for you know that's what connects everybody too is
the spirit yeah it's like whatever it has or most people have it's Holy Spirit I think it's like
that's like what animates us what is the Holy Spirit in a lot of Hinduism they'll say they'll
have a corpse and then the other God is like like sitting on the corpse and meditating or something
it means like our human body is basically just a dead body and it's like the spirit is like
what animates us and it's like so you know almost look at like a separate being or you can look at
it like it's integrated within us but it's like it is and I do think it is a feminist spirit for men
that that animates the men and maybe a masculine for women and this is Carl going to Carl Jung
theory about the onomatomous but you know men have this inner feminine it's usually one woman
but he can project it onto many different women, especially women that are kind of like blank
screens. You know, if there's some women that are just very ambiguous, like a fairy kind of
quality, it's like, what is she? Is she this? Is she this? Right? She can be a billion different
things. And so we can, people can project this onto their own onima onto this woman.
And then, but then when you're putting the power of your onima into an outside source,
Then it's a rogue onima that means that because it's like the woman that can control up the onima
And so it's that you're just projecting on sir. So it's like you can be very dangerous
I don't get some pittalls and such that
What is onima the onima is the inner feminine of a male and so it's like and so oftentimes
He'll project it out as like some other woman like the woman he falls in love with
But the real power is realizing it's actually him
and
It's his inner feminine power, but a lot of times men repress this inner feminine
And so they projected outwards on to other women and then they consider women evil and then
it will be like a
self-fulfilling prophecy then they'll be attracting these
femme fatale types and or poison women and a lot of it is based on just like Freud said
Your relationship with your mother and stuff like that when you're young, you know
Freud and Jung did have very different sounds. It sounds a lot like Ziggy
Ziggy has a feminine side. He's like, he's like, oh like, you know, like you women and you know, like you're all stupid and shit like that
And it's like, does he realize he is like half a woman?
I mean, not just, it's not just him.
Men are half women.
Like we were born of a man and a woman.
We like have one sex because we're a dual, dual species.
But what is the difference between males and females?
Really, we both can see-
The X, Y chromosomes?
Right, but we both contain the aspects of each.
Like, because we're born of each,
we're born of a male and a female.
And, you know, right?
Everybody is, everybody.
And so it's like, there is a, and why are these most straight men will be attracted to very feminine women, right?
And it's like, isn't that weird? Like, they don't like anything else feminine in life except the woman, right?
Everything else they'll like put into like oh, this is man stuff then the woman they'll put all the feminine stuff into and they'll say
Oh, that's my wife, but the secretly that's that's really them projecting out onto a person. That's what's scary
That's pretty interesting
Interesting perspective
Right, and this is Carl Carl Jung if you look in Carl Jung. He was a German
Psychologist basically one of the fathers of modern psychiatry psychology
Along with Sigmund Freud, there were a couple of German guys that had some ideas. They didn't really have any kind of idea of psychology before
Well, I don't know like it also sounds pretty occultish like at the same time it is
Carl Jung was very into the occult
He has a book called the red book and he has these
Illustrations and he also went into the dream state and talked to like certain archetypal figures
Like I think he talked to Salome and John the Baptist or something or the ones he saw
They could just as well be like Lilith and Adam or you know, it's like there's a lot of these archetypes of
that are within everybody, right? We all come from a similar thing. We're all different.
It comes out in different ways, but we are a pretty fascinating species. We're the most
complicated species of the entire universe, I think. The human brain is the most complicated
organism in the
Universe that we found so far I think our own brains, right? You like young miss Liz
Yeah, I've been listening from Australia. They got Karoli is he's very
Like a little like, you know cute little like German professor like oh
He's very but here's what's interesting. Um, right the on a mess. So females have an inner male. It's called the on a mess
Actually, I could show you like a little video. It's like it's just a short thing about but it's on of us because it's really interesting
The on this is actually like it turns into like
A group of men rather than just one man, you know, the man will see one onima women will have
We will have the group of men so let me see if I can pull this up
I wish I could find this other video, but I used to have it was so good, but
Here's the on them on in this video. Good old smoke right away. It always says okay
Okay, the camera fell. Yeah the camera fell
Um, let's see, the Anima and Anima, um, know your Anima, Anima?
You know what it reminds me of? It reminds me of you. Have you seen like the Baphomet statue? Like...
Yeah, it is Baphomet. It's Baphomet, yes.
Yeah, like it's like a male and female at the same time. It's like very weird.
It's so big right now too, like the transgenderism.
Um, that is like that is part of the whole plan. I'm right. It's like that's like the whole bottom of the thing was about transgender
It was about and now we're living in it, right?
Now we're like, yeah, pretty pretty evil to me
very very interesting. Um
I really want to find this one thing about the
um, the on the mist because it's so interesting. It's like it will tell you it's a short little thing about
Exactly what because there's this movie with Kerry Grant and
Okay, okay, just give me one second. I'll find it. I need to go to the website. It's good YouTube
but I would say look into like things like
Like Jungian psychology. It's like if you would you want to explore some of these things it is
Super oh, I don't know cuz I don't I don't believe in the occult
But um all the all occult means is like
Hidden right and so it's like secret teachings. It's like something that's hidden away
It's like it's like yeah, I I don't like things that are hidden
You know, I prefer things, you know that come to light, you know like into everybody like that's the thing
It's like they're hidden to like things that are true
Right, but there's things that are
True that are not widely known to be true. I mean, it's hard to explain, but
You know, it's like
It's just the onus possession. Okay. Is that okay? That's you sure know a lot about the occult though
I do because I've been sitting the coast since I was like eight years old like literally like oh dang
long time I
But the satanic Bible is one of my first books. I bought it. I got delayed the bookstore was like you. Oh my gosh
I remember when I wanted that shit like
Yeah, when I was younger because like when you're younger it's like edgy and it's interesting. Yeah, and that was like rebellious
You know, you get all those religious stuff down our throat and stuff and it's like it's interesting to like
All of a sudden we go to that we go to the opposite. We go to the most extreme opposite of it, right?
Yeah, it's pretty interesting. Okay. I'm almost I have to tell you I think why you and I'll show you sometime the art that he did
It's like so
I mean, the argument was just like, I found, okay, I found it.
Oh, okay.
So this is just the oneness.
Okay.
So this is about the.
So, so JT says to him, good and evil are definitely not the same.
They're not the same, but they're on the same pole.
They're, they're on the same.
They are the same.
They actually are the same thing basically because.
Evil is like an absence of all good or something that good is an absence of evil
But they're on the same pole just like love and hate are on the same pole
So if you hate somebody that's actually loving them because yeah, like the duality thing the
Exactly so here's a bit check this out. This is the this is about the anonymous and see if this makes any sense to you
Okay, and Sikin said appear to you. Okay. Okay. We're gonna watch a little movie sick. It's just a few minutes long. Okay. Just watch this. Oh
there he is
Every woman there was a masculine aspect in her psyche the archetype of the animus and for every man
feminine counterpart the anima
The anima is an archetype
An archetype for expressing the fact that a man
has a minority of feminine or female genes and that is something that doesn't disappear
in him, that is constantly present and it works as a female in a man. The same is the
case with the animals that is a masculine image in a woman's mind.
which is sometimes quite conscious, sometimes it's not conscious, but it is calling to life
the moment that woman meets a man who says the right things.
And then because he says it is all true, he is the fellow, no matter what he is.
Now that's not a generally accepted idea because the old hangover of
You lean on men and men will somehow
make your life interesting or something and
You just lose all your own ideas or
innovations or
Creativity and I think a lot of women are scared out of being
who they are and doing whatever is important to them.
Still, the animus to me is one of the most significant concepts that has arisen in Jungian psychology.
and personhood, her creativity, the unform that's forming as she ages, her work, her word, her ideas, herself, her person.
In the Alfred Hitchcock film, Matorious, John B.D. finds a drama of the animus in the conflict between a woman and men.
We'd like a statement from you, Mr. Huberman, about your father. For instance, if your father got what he deserved,
could we say that you're pleased your father's going to pay the penalty for being a German worker?
Now, notice the way the woman is badgered by a series of men.
All the people holding cameras are men, and all the people who speak to her are men, and
so you immediately get the image of a woman in a vulnerable position, badgered by a group
or a series of men.
Now, there's the perfect image of what your means by the onimist, the way the onimist
by a multiple figure or a crowd and the way it moves in on the woman and judges her.
The cameras are all in the lower left hand of the screen.
And then gradually, we realize that in the lower left hand,
there is now one man whose viewpoint we have,
and he's a dark, kind of unknown figure.
She's half attracted to him, half suspicious of him,
and he's a policeman.
This is the experience of so many women
of constantly being under an attack.
Do I look okay? Is my reputation okay?
The camera turns and finally he becomes a personality on his own right.
Indeed, he's carried Grant.
There's one more drink left to be saved about the ice.
So the very critic, the very thing that's most attacking the woman, is also somehow the thing that's most erotically exciting, and the most interesting, and the most energetic, and there, in a little nutshell, you get the problem of the anonymous.
Falling in love at first sight, that is such a case.
You see you have a certain image in yourself without doing it, of the woman, of the real woman.
Now you see that girl, or at least a good imitation of your life.
And constantly you get the seizure and lock down.
And afterwards you may discover that he was a terrible mistake.
The concepts of animus and anima emerged as Jung observed the lives and psychological realities of
his patients and they helped him understand both the pain and the delights of human relationship.
Robert Johnson. Man insists upon making some outer figure, generally a flesh and blood woman,
anima for him. That is, he mediates the outer world by way of his anima instead of using
their inside where she belongs.
This produces more suffering and more upset and more pain than any other single thing that I know about
That she's a head of a business, and until he dares me so, I will say,
for proud trade officer helps me to get it.
The head of that heaven? He can't.
Please, please, can I pay you nothing?
That is the only help.
That is all about the fact of the anima.
This contribution of young glanimous nanomouth theory is not only of immense use in understanding
relationship difficulties and the joys and rations of relationships, but it's actually something,
as with all the best ideas, that people, ordinary people, are doing anyway.
That's a real acid test of all psychological theory.
If it really turns out to be a description of what's happening, it's good theory.
Mm-hmm. What do you think? Did you get that or is it too too too much or what?
Um, I feel like it needs to be explained a little bit better. Okay. Well, I mean just the basic
Explanation of it like like a like an example like an example is that
A man will fall in love with a woman
That is like not good for it. He'll know it's not good for anything. He won't be able to fall out of luck
It's because it's actually spalling love with himself. He's projecting his own inner feminine onto this woman
who's image is an imitation of something in his mind as archetype that he has in his mind and
Just like clay in her hands like because she is
So women and men work together. It's like not just like men are the creative ones women are not like it's like without the other one like
But like we need both right hey summer. How are you doing? It's just you know found it interesting
Yeah, I will try to explain it better
I did it I did do a presentation on my last channel about the Anima on this
I might just like a pair to do that one again because it is um I give more examples than that
But that but it's interesting about the woman feeling attacked by her on a miss or intermasculine
It's like so it appears like a group of men, right? It's like and there's all these
instances of a woman saying, oh, this happened with this group of men attack or, you know,
or it feels attacked by certain men as a whole or whatever. But she's also most sexually attracted
to this conflict. And so it's, I mean, so that makes it difficult, right? It's like,
the person that's most driving her crazy is the one she's most attracted to. I'm not sure of
relationships though. I mean, it's, it's really funny. It is. Hey, Summer. Okay. So yeah, well,
yeah um so yeah yeah I'm I'm finding it a little hard to understand but I kind of
like get it
There's a great presentation I used to watch and it's about it. I don't think I can find it anymore
But I kept looking for it, but it's like it does give the best explanation. You can't decide for it
Okay, too much mental gymnastics. It is it's interesting. I mean, it's like if you are in touch with your inner feminine
Or your inner masculine, it'll be a lot easier to understand
Especially if it's like you because yeah, men need women and women need men. That is true
Right, but it's like in a way that it's like they manifest together, right? Oh J
So are there ones to link? Oh, no, JT wants one JT wants to talk to us. Okay, let's see
I did pure real quick. So I'll be right back. You talk to the chapter once I got some people quick. Okay. Yeah, JT you like he
He likes this kind of stuff
Oh, gosh, okay, is that the JT here?
No, he's not here yet.
Okay.
He's not here yet?
Not here yet.
Come on up, JT, I need you to stop sharing this.
Yeah, JT likes this kind of stuff.
Like he'll also give you like his insights, his input.
Yeah, I love psychology.
Yeah, I'm not, you know, I always like,
Been super egg, you know, I was yeah, he does too. He likes psychology and stuff like that
But he doesn't he tells me he doesn't necessarily agree with you know young and you know like
Yeah, the the famous
Philosopher psychologist and all right a lot of it's from like, you know ancient Greece there's philosophy and stuff like that from ancient Greece
Let me see if I can find some, A, I, M, A, let me see.
I can't find it, I can't find it, but I would love to though.
But it is super interesting, especially like,
if you look into the red book guys,
you can like look into the red book
and it is very enlightening.
Okay, is this it?
Red book?
Yeah, it's called the red book.
Is this
Okay, there's Collie right there. Okay, so I think JT's coming up. Let's see
Yes, well, that's oh, that's here our friend
With this like he
With us like he hello with us like he
Oh, you guys are talking about the animus. Yeah, do you know about them a little bit little bit?
You know, I have like a cursor understanding like well basically that every man and woman has like
Like an aspect of themselves that is of the opposite gender base, right?
The inner feminine or inner masculine. Yeah, walka walka queen. Yep. She's the walka walka queen
Some more than others clearly, right? Right?
Gays sometimes they say your anima must be like through the roof, huh?
Yeah, he shook over like she's like the anima could take over the inside too, you know
And so that that can happen too
I think that happens a lot with like transgender people is like the anima just totally takes over the man, right?
And it's anything he becomes her right and as much as he can do I think it's better
It's good to have a balance, you know my anima is
I think I have a very, I do have a feminine mind.
I think I do think like a woman a lot of the way,
like a lot of the way I think is like,
I think like a woman, like a woman's brain
or something like that.
And that I'm intuitive or I'm receptive.
I'm like, but I have both sides.
So I really do.
You're more like, more like empathetic.
Yeah, we must scribe certain traits to like either male or female, which in a way is kind
of true.
But I don't think that they're exclusive either, like, they're not because there's men with
that.
We both have all these traits.
It's just that there's certain traits that are like, encouraged for men to have and then
it's for women to have and not for men or for men to have enough for women.
And so we're told, Oh, this is male.
This is the guy.
This is the girl.
That's how it's supposed to be.
you know, organized and categorized things that are like,
kind of necessarily that easy to categorize,
but pretty interesting.
I mean, they're traditionally masculine traits
and they're traditionally feminine traits, right?
And everybody knows what that means.
Right, but like men are not.
encouraged in our culture to like to cry or to express like you know feelings as much as like
women are like because women are just like emotional ninjas they're experts at like
their feelings they've been they've already been they were the men are like told oh don't go that's
one that's a woman's territory that's like the women's stuff and like so I think in general and
it may be like hormonal or whatever I think there's clearly player difference I think women tend to
Not that men don't feel emotions, but they seem to feel them like more. I don't know.
Yeah, they do feel stronger. Their senses are stronger too, because they're like more of a copy,
or like more of a, I would say, they resonate more with the whole universe, because it's like
they are like the earth where they feel more they're more in touch with like their senses they
see more colors like a man sees like the colors of the rainbow like you know five red blue yellow
green yellow whatever women see like you know maroon violet you know magenta i mean there's
just a billion colors they see right they think that's because they can discern these little
differences right um because they're more sensitive to senses that they sense more they just feel more
we are being a little bit stereotypical, but yeah.
I mean, I do believe they feel stronger.
They also, they feel childbirth
and so they are like better adapted to like some kinds of pain.
Like men are kind of more babies about pain than like,
I remember my dad would stub his toe.
He'd be like, oh my, he'd be like on the ground screaming.
My mom would like, you'd go through like some sort,
you know, she'd be like stoic and fine,
no matter what, but my dad would be like, oh my God, my toe.
So it's like, there's like these little,
There's these differences. I don't know if I'm explaining it right, but
But yeah, right that's pretty much the gist of the idea or the concept of it
It's basically like men have like a feminine part of them and women have like a masculine part of them somewhere
Do you agree with the anima and the animus?
Do I agree with it?
Is that the
Do I yeah, do I agree with like the concept of it? I understand where they're coming from
But do I agree with it the way they the way it's exactly presented not exactly like I think I think people are complex
And they have difference, you know many different aspects of them to consider to consider them feminine or masculine
Um, because they're talking about energy. They're talking about something a little bit more
Here's a I found a three minute. I didn't find the one I was looking for right
I didn't find a three minute thing about the onima and this like maybe if it once you understand the onima the onimus
Kind of becomes easier to understand. I'll just play this quick little three minute video, but the onima is this called
it says
The the secret woman inside every man. Okay, so I share it and then we'll
Just have a look at this video, and then that'll be
I'm gonna go ahead and say I don't have a secret woman like hidden. It's
Don't rain like he has he's hiding a woman inside there. Okay, so
But here we go like check check this out
I think this will be a good explanation for that just it's like a yeah pretty good video. Okay, so here we go
I boil
Or the Justin what's up Justin
Tell us what you said what's up. You see it
What if the woman you dream about isn't real but a mirror of your soul
The anima and animus are the fundamental archetypes within young's theory of the unconscious
They represent the contraceptual aspects of the psyche
Understanding these two concepts is crucial for grasping young's idea about psychological wellness and the dynamics of relationships
Watch this video as it explores the anima archetype
In short, the anima is the feminine aspect in the male psyche, meaning it is the unconscious
feminine side of a man.
This doesn't mean having feminine traits in a superficial sense, but rather a deeply
rooted archetype which represents the totality of the feminine psychological possibilities
within the man.
The anima, according to Yilm, is a complex of emotions, intuition, moods, receptivity
It manifests in man's feelings, sensibilities, his capacity for love and empathy, and his
understanding of relationships.
It may appear in dreams as a mysterious woman, seductress, guide, or a spiritual companion.
The animal develops throughout a man's life, often initially during his relationship with
his mother.
That means that an early positive relationship with mothers can contribute to a more integrated
and healthy anima, while a difficult and overly dominant maternal figure can lead to a more
negative and problematic anima development.
Later relationships with other women also contribute to the anima development.
The anima develops in four stages.
Number one, Eve.
Eve represents the mother archetype.
2. Helen or Helen of Troy. It embodies romantic and aesthetic femininity and the beauty that can inspire passion, but sometimes lead to conflict.
3. Mary. Mary represents the spiritual and devotional femininity in connection to higher values.
4. Sophia. The last stage represents wisdom and understanding.
Every man develops the anima in various ways, both positively and negatively.
A positive manifestation of the anima is when it leads to qualities like emotional intelligence, creativity, sensitivity and a capacity for deep connection,
and most importantly a balanced understanding of both masculine and feminine perspectives.
A well-integrated anima can inspire artistic expression, spiritual insights and a richer inner life.
On the other hand, a negative manifestation of the anima project itself onto women in the external world.
When the anima is repressed or negatively developed, it can lead to unrealistic idealization of women,
or conversely, seeing women as irrational, manipulative, or overly emotional.
A negative anima manifests as moodiness and insecurity.
It can also lead to a man feeling feminine in a negative, emasculating way.
Lastly the goal isn't to suppress or worship the animal but to integrate her
So have you met your anima or are you still chasing her in the world?
Thank you guys for your time
Okay
Hey DJ Electra, I feel like you're in high school. You're falling asleep Justin. Oh well
Yeah, like the thing is um jt doesn't believe in like yong's teachings like the archetypes and stuff like that
I don't know where he gets this stuff. I know I know where a lot of he gets
like you think that JT thinks that you know people are more complex than that you know like the archetypes you know just putting
People are so complex that we might as well say okay
Let's not have an understanding of anything but we can't come to some general ideas with these things like I'm saying
It's like a very useful thing to understand that
we have a feminine side, we're going to have a masculine side, and we can project these qualities of
ourselves through oppression onto other people. And we can actually just like sometimes when you're
with a narcissist in a relationship, right, you will start to fall in love with them. But what they
do is they mirror you in the certain parts of the relationship. And so they're mirroring you. And so
when you're not, you're not falling in love with them, you're falling in love with yourself because
they're just mirroring you back to yourself. And so that's the really insidious part of it. Hey,
It's just jibberish Justin Boyle, but you're jibberish. Go a good jibberish ever.
It's funky. I'm sorry you have to do this guy.
No, I mean, I understand the point of archetypes. It's like a basically a way to kind of simplify or
like recognize the patterns. Yeah, we have all of them, but we can represent more like the tool.
There's a tool album called anima. Yeah, the anima anima. Yeah, it's very similar words, right?
You know what architect is, right?
Like you know like like a category you put somebody in
Yeah
But it's like I mean there's a tradition there's like a hero archetype there's like a wizard archetype
There's like the father archetype. There's all the other doctors as a healer
There's a there's all these different kind of like, you know categories and stuff
It is helpful in recognizing that there's these universal categories that a lot of people can fit into you, right?
Justin go to hell. I mean go to hell. He's just fucking with you. He's
Just he's just trolling. No, I mean a lot of people like
If it becomes a subject that doesn't interest you
If it comes out as gibberish, maybe your brain is gibberish, okay?
Right because a lot of people are dumb, right, but it's like, you know,
It's because a lot of people don't take the time to try to understand
You're boring, Justin. You're boring me. You and KZ are go
Go get gay marry each other. Please get out of my life and into each other's. I mean, Jesus, cry me
Well, never mind.
Anyway, I know, I don't want him to leave Spunky for KZ,
that'd be a man.
No, it's kind of like the theory of forms in a way,
but it applies to people.
It's like, basically, there's an original.
Right, but people are all different,
but they're all the same.
Have you noticed that?
There's a universal thing behind being a human, right?
Hey, Summer, I want you to learn KZ.
I want you to learn that you're an asshole
and you're annoying.
You're an asshole, Summer.
And I think you're learning it slowly, KZ.
Anyway, just saying that your brain is fried but but I am seeing a lot of like the negative stuff
You know like in Ziggy because he didn't have a good relationship with his mother and so he's over here, you know like
being very
How do I say an asshole to Jan?
Dude, honestly, I wouldn't say that has much to do with the anima animus concept
I think it's just fucking classic mommy issues like you know fucking
Your relationship with your mother will affect your relationship with women in general don't don't you think so?
I mean, it's like, oh, of course. Yeah, absolutely
100%
You're way than any other relationship because it's like with the mud that's where Freud and him kind of like agreed is that like
You know, there's a lot of importance in these relationships, but the only way they differ
was that Freud put it more in a sexual sense, like he's like, oh, you're in love with your
mother and blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I don't I don't know about
Yeah, this complex or the electric complex the electric complexes and I'm falling in love with your father
There's a similar
It is
Electra, yeah
Exactly, but oh here we have somebody else coming on stage this welcome to our panel. Oh
Look who it is. Oh gosh. Oh
Are you okay, say
See is he ever seen your mom through a home and got out on about the son mother. What?
It's a song
Okay, thanks for her like yeah, yeah, she knows she knows
What yeah, it's called a grand baron
w
Good Johnny. I'm listening to that right now. You know what w is w is equals
The number 23
It's a pretty messed up song though. Like the game. It's a sad song, but it is all cheery and stuff like that, you know
More historical a lot of those punks down way more history man. I mean
Yeah, it is a sad song
But it sounds happy though. Yeah, so Katie thinks in here
Well, I don't KZ doesn't want to know what I think about him. So I mean, it's like, you know, well, I think I do
Yeah, we know anything about KZ. He's a windbag
Okay, I'm sorry. That was rude
Boyle behavior, I'm telling spunky
Where I'm gonna get spunky on speed dial right now spunky your your your fiance's misbehaving
You're a jerk. No, it's okay guys. If you don't understand it just means
You're dumb
It just means how I just like listen a little bit like think about it
It's like it takes a while to understand
You're being introduced to things that maybe
Yeah, I've been before maybe instead of like, you know saying I'm speaking gibberish
We I do know some things, you know, I don't know every I don't know
So psyche, do you agree with a lot of young's teachings?
Yes, a lot of them, because a lot of this to do with the unconscious and the subcon-
like the- and I believe that the subconscious and unconscious are largely ruling our personalities
and our actions, you know, of what we're not even aware of, right? It's like kind of like
the instinctual autopilot parts of ourselves that we take for granted, right?
He was definitely into dreams, like dream interpretation, dreaming.
He was into active visualization.
He's into like using art as like a emotional outlet and self-discovery.
He was into all that.
And so he's super interesting.
He's very, very interesting.
I like him better than Freud.
I do like him better than Freud, because Freud was a little bit too like into like the
JT doesn't agree with Freud either.
Okay, well yeah.
Freud sounds like they were fraud, right, doesn't it?
And I think like a lot of psychology is just gibberish, gibberish, jabber.
But listen, Young is very, very, very smart.
I mean, and it's like also the art that he produced,
he wasn't necessarily like consider himself the most talented artist,
but the art he produced, like spiritually,
is somewhat like the most amazing art I've ever seen.
there's this immense like powerhouse behind like understanding this stuff that
there's there's so much creativity untapped in us that we don't even realize
that we're capable of so much we are we actually we're actually capable of
godlike things that we are very very very unrecognizing of that so our
power is you know got a leash on a little bit but we can't like start
No, I wasn't gonna say anything
Come on JC. Say it. Just say it. No, I actually wasn't going to
Okay, well
Yeah, well spunky is gonna spank you now Justin change her name to spanky and she's gonna do it to you. Okay
Justin just in boil. She's gonna pop the boil. Okay. That's a that's a bad
So it would be a bad thing to change your name to shot in the chest
I must have a shot
Loaded like with like a gun
Like like excuse me excuse me
Shut your fat mouth what I mean, okay
I appreciate the compliment excuse me what I mean to say what I mean to say is
Projectile high-speed projectile object. Yeah, it's a better
You said listen see you literally just said the word I didn't say it I'm saying a high-speed
Projectile object put a chop under your chest. You just said right the way he's no
He's not much like anymore. So I didn't say that you did
Wait did
What channel by the way, I don't remember
JT's asking what happened to the other
That on purpose why is this guy yelling because I'm saying something fucking idiot
Because he's a drunk because I'm fucking speaking are you like what?
We were literally having a discussion before
All right, well, here's the thing buddy, we were literally having a conversation
Your mic is just like louder than everybody. All right, congratulations, buddy. There's something you can hit the volume down button
I'm not talking to you psyche. I'm talking to this fucking idiot over here
Okay, so this guy wants to be saying oh your volume is too loud turn it down
Nobody gives a saying right. Nobody ever give you give a shit then you turn it down dumbass
Okay, hey drugs
You talk to one drunk you talk to all yeah, that is true
So you're like real quiet about the the other channel, like I'm not real quiet
The other channel is gone. I can't do anything about it. It's deleted. I mean, I understand it sucks. It hurts. Whatever
Feel more free to like say what I want now, but no way. Yeah in a way
I talked to psyche about it earlier. He said basically somebody porn bombed her. Yeah
He didn't have any strikes
I didn't have any strikes. Yeah, they take it down the first time and that's that was kind of
Weird about it because they usually have hidden strikes. I didn't have any strikes. No, I didn't have any strikes
Yeah, I've just never heard of a channel being removed without strikes. Yeah good times and betas the same thing at exact
Really? Wow
Yeah without strikes. That's crazy
Thanks. Yep
And with the videos private and stuff like that. So I mean it can't happen unfortunately, but you know, it's just part of it
I'm a lot of people whoever whoever poor mommy had a part in because it was like some thing that was probably on some old video that they
You know you don't know who I'm gonna say was Alex McQueen
Yes, yo psyche remember the guy 300
Yeah, yeah, the Q guy. He literally I mean, I'm not gonna I'm not gonna like agree with what you just said
Okay, but psyche right at the 300 guy
Literally this guy
Just went to Target. He's he got in it. He got a ps5 for free
He literally no no no he didn't steal it what he did was he went through the he went through the check the check thing whenever
the machine
He got a 36 pack of water and he put a ps5 through it
No, that's not stealing he paid for it
No, he paid for it. What are you talking about? That's not stealing
That's not stealing he paid for it in the barcode for the water instead of the PlayStation. Yeah, he totally stole it. No
No, you tripping
That's not what I said. He paid for the ps5
For the water then a good 300 glow paid for the ps5 shout out to him. He figured out the system
Shout out shout out to 300 glow he paid he paid five dollars instead of 500
the
never stupid ass
why would psyche get arrested
tripping ass
oh yeah I don't even know
you ask me
sounds like a dumb drunk stick
what is wrong with you
I sound like a retarded and homosexual drunk man
yes you do
You mean W but I still make sense
It's like you said you're gayer than him
Homosexual man shout out to him. Yeah, half the motherfuckers you bring up here gayer than you psyche. I don't know how that works
W you don't even know
Like they don't even know we're gay with you you don't even know
I've been to get I've been to the gay parade, bro, I was in the gay parade like
2013 I
Forgot what year were you in a leather man? I wasn't not on the hell. No, bro. I was I was with gay friends
Okay, let's go. Let's give him like I was like 20 20 2014 15
I forget by yourself didn't you no
I won't like gay friends because they were all games and they were like all pull up sick
Oh, we're gonna be like it's gonna be lit. Whatever and was it was crazy, bro
Everybody so everybody's all naked and shit
Do you like it's just out here? We're here to the bitches out there. We're titties out gay dudes out there
You know what I mean being a last naked and shit
Did I like it? I mean I
Wouldn't say I like it, but it was an interesting experience to see a bunch of fucking naked people
I guess that's an interesting experience
Did you prefer that the naked? Let's go. I guess interest interesting is a good way of saying like
of the
I mean, I'm the chubby guy now, but I'll tell you now, in those years I was in top shape, absolutely no one to be jealous of.
You mean eating her banana again?
Oh, did you eat someone's banana steak?
That's crazy.
Who's banana?
Okay, well bananas are these things. Well, who has ownership over bananas because they come out of the earth
Chiquita company owns them. I think right who runs it in the Monsanto seat, right?
Well, I mean, I guess these particular like crops, but I mean like
Yeah, the concept of the banana who owns it
They have bananas, they have bananas in Indonesia.
It's a woman with like, she wears a basket of fruit on her head.
They do have bananas, they do have bananas in Indonesia.
They have bananas in Indonesia.
I've been there, and I remember I almost got T-boned by a scooter.
It was the most terrifying thing and funniest thing ever.
You almost got teabag by a cooter. What'd you say? No, I almost got t-boned by a scooter with maybe like five people on it
For
We're in Indonesia. Yeah in Indonesia facts
OK, well, he just says stuff just to just
Vietnam and Indonesia is the same thing.
OK, might as well be the same thing.
No, they're literally like I'm going to I'm pulling over.
And like, dude, these countries where it's just scooters,
it's in it's in it's an insanity.
There are there are hardly any regulations.
There's no traffic signals.
You literally just like, OK, I'm going to go to the gas station.
I'm gonna pull over to the rest like there's no like
Traffic signals or nothing like people just go in the direction of what they're going right?
Well, I mean you should
Psyche you should go to Vietnam and stream in Vietnam. That should be
I mean, yeah, pretty much like any like East yeah East Asian country is lit
And it will be pretty cheap usually probably and you won't you probably won't have problems
I know Vietnam. They don't give you trouble
Like Cambodia if you go to Cambodia as an American, they will give you problems being I won't
Are you saying?
Are you gonna go with me into your bed?
I mean
I'm not against going to East Asia. Okay, not against that. That would be cool
I don't think it would I don't think I'm it would intend on sharing a bed with you
I'll get a queen
You know many times the guys go to Thailand, of course you go to Asia. Have you been to Thailand sick?
I've never been no, you know what he's there for
I've never I don't think I've I've been only to the furthest I've been is South America
You want to visit the lady boys in Thailand? Oh, you know it?
No, I don't think I don't think that would be my goal
I mean if I wanted a lady boy, I could just go for psyche. I mean, I'm not a lady
And you know what the lady boys in Thailand can kick your fucking ass. They're mostly kickboxers. Did you know that?
Yeah, I know, you know funny enough
Psyche funny enough. I was on this stream with this guy like this like old guy. I
Don't know. Maybe like 60 70s. I forget
And he was he was speaking about his experience in Thailand and people are you talking are you are you talking about Wiggins?
No
It was somebody else and so it's this guy
It's this guy that he was talking about how he he spent like I don't even know I think he spent deck
I think he said decades even in in Thailand
And he said like people were joking like oh lady boys, whatever they made a joke and he was like oh, no
I don't the lady boys are trouble like he was like super serious
No, he said he said like he he worked in a cafe or some shit like that or some shit
And and and he said that the lady boys would all be the source of the trouble they would get into fights
they would get it, they would do trouble, whatever, they were the source of the trouble
they're mad, they're mad in a way
uh, they're fucking dudes
well yeah
look at the way Mikey's sitting right now
yeah
obviously
I'm not sitting
right
he's making an attempt
he's making his best attempt
I think he's trying to seduce you, Sig, is it working?
I mean, I think maybe you could step it up a little bit, but not quite there.
No, I mean, I think you need to put a little makeup on.
Say, have you ever, see Aztec warrior got me and she didn't even have to try.
You know what I mean?
Maybe, maybe because she's a woman, like an actual woman.
Hey man, are you up with the white guys?
Have you?
And would you like to try?
You might help.
You know, if you're not gay.
I think I lost him.
Oh, you want the link?
What did you say?
Would you ever have sex with me?
300 wants the link.
Can we not?
I don't think I would do that.
But can we not jump to these extreme questions?
Yes, we have to.
Hold on. Where is steering globe?
I need I need my uh no the other guy these questions are sort of like this is like a
Late late moment. This is like the last question you ask, you know, I mean
So say
Let's continue to have conversations. You know, I mean, yes or no to say yes or no
You're you're not drunk. Well, I'm ever not drunk. Absolutely. I am also sober at many times. I'm also the time of my life
I'm sober
Because obviously I don't joins I don't dream these panels and I'm sober
Would you answer the question for yourself?
Excuse me go on chatter bait with Chris K me and 300 blow
All together. Are you saying if I want to do that? Oh, what is the question?
Would I do that hmm, yes, I'm gonna say
I'm going to say no for right now. You know what I mean? I'm open to accepting offers
I'm gonna say no right now though
He's like it up his leg for you I understand
I'm sure that he's putting it behind his head.
He's putting both legs behind his head for you.
This is great.
Well, see, here's the thing, though.
I want to see Rain put both her legs above her head.
That's what I want to see.
That's more of the direction that I'm looking at.
Oh, you did the heart to me.
Oh, shit, we got two drugs for the price of one.
It's doing it hard, but it's a W.
Oh
My money's gonna find out where you hide out. I'm gonna bring down myself
Okay, you better take your shirt off or you're kicking off the show
Not a moment of hesitation for him to get gay as far immediately
Please get gay everyone. Let's get gay. That's one thing I could say about signal. I've never seen him doing some overtly gay shit
Well, I have
Have done
the
Jesus
No, how are his feet dirty because the fucking floor is dirty
Yeah, well, I'm gonna sit next to 300 listen, you know who'd you go over there get glow over there to fucking mop your floor without a shirt off
Three are glow. Would you come over when Chris K and I are doing chatterbait and join us?
Maybe signal do it
You were slippers in your home? Well, that's gay. I don't work. I do a Japanese style where I'm barefoot
You were slippers when you miss a Roger dude if your floors are clean, it doesn't matter if you're bare
Okay, anyway, I'm gonna play I'm gonna play a music video to cleanse our palate
New song guys get ready
Yeah, I wear slippers too.
I don't listen to you.
I listen to you.
you came bleeding stories beg for a shrine but i can't be a savior when i'm crossing my own line
to the black where the current owns you never felt the pull beneath your skin so
back to the deep where you belong before you drown
that's not about that was about my sharing myself open to see
how I feel my scars and so big time thinks you were being
secretly mean to me I didn't pick up on who who who who's
that? Who are you being mean to me? Of course not. I mean, I
mean, I actually mod you. I'm not I don't mod just Oh my.
See, I didn't have this time. See?
Yeah, you know what they say.
If you like the music, think you think it is.
Well, if you like him, you have to mod me, too.
Oh, yeah, we're like a two for one kind of thing.
We're like a two pack.
Well, I trust it. I trust it. You just can't like, you know.
We'll do anything crazy, you know.
I won't dox kids or whatever the fuck.
I've been...
Oh, yeah. Everybody needs to do this.
Oh, my gosh. Please, I'm too.
I know. Fun times.
Okay, okay, so I'm well to be fair Wiggins. Doc's his own kid. No
You know, we won't we won't bring up those those dark times
The dark chapter happier in all our lives. Yeah, I'm moving on to happier better things
Mods everybody secretly hey, that's that's good
I'll keep your friends close keep your enemies. Let me just get
Yeah, that's what they know like I invited psyche to our CFF discord. Did you join a psyche?
I'm going to write. Oh, yeah in the back chat. Well, technically, I'm in your discord. So you might as well
You are my discord. Oh, okay. I know I'm just not very well your discord is not very but he has to join our server now
I have to but he can't if you like
No, he is because he's an official member of cff. He's the chat. He's the cff priest
Oh, he's the high the high priestess the high priest
Well, you know because the anima is like so powerful, right, but yeah, and I have a very powerful she's
Actually, it's extremely powerful. Oh, hold on a second. Oh, did I comment? I don't know if I can I have to okay?
That's what it is. It's because when I
Have the gaming and then that the normal
I'll just put a comment.
You can't so choose to verify something else.
Okay, got it.
Use password key.
Okay, no, verify something else.
He's back up.
Okay, I'm going to get into this.
I'm sorry.
It's making me to go through a hoops right now.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, yeah.
For our server, you have to apply.
Like you just put a reason why you want to join in.
I said, like, I mean, it's a log in and then it's like saying,
okay, well, you have to like go get a code from like your other account.
Yeah, you got another password.
Yeah, okay, I know where it is. So it's right here and that's on that. Okay. Where is it that and privacy? There we go. And is it there? No, it's not. Okay. Is it under account?
Yes, actually, you know
I'm not sure how much of a loss it was, but I actually like you not being monetized
I think it's like I do too. I'm like someone who are comfortable. It's like it's so much easier
Really fucking chill. I think yeah
Do you do you have like a like a sigh of relief like it like a weight off his shoulders?
You see how like
Stressed out I was when I was watching you were strung the hell out like all the time
It's stressful. It's like
Cause it's like, no one wants to lose it, but it's like now that it's like, now it's like, now I don't have to worry about it, it's like, okay, I mean, you still got your people and I think you were, I think you're getting most of your.
Most of your stuff's coming from cash up. Anyway, you don't need that. You don't need to be fine. It's just stress verification
Now if you were like, you know, if you had like hundreds of thousands of subscribers, maybe but yeah, I mean, I didn't I mean
It's like so it's not the problem when you're like it when you're having like 1000 2000 subs like that's that's not a good spot to be because
Then you have to worry about all the stress, but you're not getting any of the fucking
revenue, but like for example, like a Lisa Jordana is
It's monetized, but she doesn't really use it like she doesn't have a membership. She doesn't ask for super chats. She just
She says do my power chat. So that's like, you know, that's like a off
YouTube thing that pays you right away all the kind of thing
I mean plus play YouTube pays once a month and it takes like a lot of the money, right? It's like dude
How many thousands of off-study? How many thousands of dollars do you think ghosts through at you it?
If you had to say like
Over at that man, I don't I don't I don't count exactly, but it's very extremely generous and
It has to be it has to be thousands say it was it was about it was at least three grand. Let's be honest
That's insane, who would you say is your highest donator if it's not that if it's not that guy I'd be shocked. I think it's him
But I have some up, but it's like, you know, I had some other very um, I don't know if everyone with their names of those so
No, if only everyone fucking came into an inheritance and was a stupidest ghost you'd be fucking loaded
I he works for only his inheritance
No, he came out of nowhere suddenly started doing this
No, yes, he's got a job. I'm not saying he doesn't I'm just saying he suddenly came into like a large amount of disposable income at once
Enough to throw at you like three at least three thousand five
Does not worry about what my hey, hey, I don't say I think get paid, you know
No shit, you're not doing anything wrong
He's really input. I say you get paid
Are you definitely a dog mask come on? I know you don't want to alienate you
My my ghost don't I still think it was ghosts that porn bombed. Why would he I mean dude?
He invested so much money in that fucking channel. Why would he well because he gets mad at psyche for no reason
Was he mad?
Yeah, he was mad when he left
What an idiot to throw that much money into something and then just like in well
Because he thinks he can control psyche's channel and tell psyche what to do. Oh, I think she can like pay for
Yeah, like that he has like special privileges
No, he's treating it like a pay pig
You're like, hey, stop talking about ghosts shut up. I don't want any more names
I mean Jesus, I mean he's like come on be nice to me the one person that's actually helping me out
Like like I don't want to feel like insulting him all night, please. Oh trust me. No, I'm actually gonna make he's gonna donate more now
Just because of this
You got to trust the process like I say I'm gonna make more on YouTube just because of I'm not monetizing. So yes
Yeah, I do believe trust the process sometimes. Okay, so now I can fit in the back of the finally
Okay, so now I can put it back down. I'm gonna join your discord in one second. So available back. Oops. Okay
P H
Peanut Sun V
I don't have penis envy. Okay. Oh shit. No, it's an invalid.
So I would actually be I would be concerned if psyche didn't yell at me at some point. So
Yes, you should be okay. So, okay, the k I need to put my other glasses.
Yeah, he's always scolding you.
He loves to yell at me. I don't know why. Okay.
Maybe it turns him on.
It does a little bit. I hope not.
Okay, this work. Oh my God, it's not working. Come on. Please work. Damn it. What's, what's
that need me to do? It's like, put it all in the lower case. What's going on here? Okay.
Yes, it worked. Okay. Now I'm in a minute. Okay. Now I can now I can click on the link in oh my god
I'm wearing two pairs of glasses. Okay, I'll be cast away if I turn them down
Are you are you joining the discord? Yes, and what should we say? Oh my god now. Let's say. I'm not even logged in yet
So, but okay. No, no here. I'm okay. What?
Please log in again. I mean, it's I think we log in. I mean, this is just ridiculous
Are you playing games right now with this? Are you trolling us? It's just taking forever. Okay
Okay
Okay, it works. Okay. Now it's asking me to verify with this to verify with something else. Okay, use a backup code
Okay, and just an eight. Okay. It got it. I got it back. Okay. It's a backup code
Drawing us, isn't it? I swear to God. I'm not I'm gonna do it the right this time. Oh my god. It's keeps asking you for more information
It's like I'm gonna need you so I'm gonna need you your phone number your social your your account and routing number. Oh my god
This is taking forever
Okay, now here it comes. Okay, it says I can copy this one pasted in that's good. Okay, here it goes
Okay, easy. Okay, perfect. No, yeah, Jamie's been in there for a little while. She's great. We love Jamie. We do love Jamie
Jamie you're the heart of the show
Yes, okay, here it is. Okay, copy this
This better work paste this in
Okay, yes, it worked. Okay now backup codes copy, okay
Okay, I can take it. Okay
L six I
Six I'm very focused on it, you know, I don't know I'm not gonna mention the wrench. He's very focused 93 K
Ah, it worked. Okay, and it's gonna say
You know what I mean, right? Where is the you can let him in. I'll let you
Doesn't work. I'm gonna click on the girl link one more time
If it tells me to log in again, I'm going to scream and just try it later. Okay, so
Discord
Okay, it keeps logging me. Okay, I'll just do it later. Okay. Oh my god, this is just to rain. He's pulling our leg
He's throwing Disney
Not surely just keeps asking me to enter over and over again. I don't have the thousands of years to do this
I mean, it's like you but hey, hey JT. Can you just invite me be at a discord?
If you're my discord, you can invite me. Oh, I guess. Yeah, I actually could do that. Yeah, why the hell not? Yeah, invite him to there
Yeah, that would be a easier yeah, yes
We're psyche
There are you a good book instead of words Waldo. We're thank you new little pieces
Looking for him right now, okay, it's thank you. Wake it. No, no, it's actually called the psyche. Yeah
Yeah, let me see
Have you added to a friend as a friend, let me see if I could put you in my search
Oh here we go. See you. Now I can. Yeah, there you go. I just sent it to you right now. Open application. Why do I want him to join?
Can I put it to seduce Ziggy?
I'm going to put that as the answer. Does that work?
Okay. My application is pending.
is it? Yeah, JT will let you in. Oh my god. I saw this picture. So Jamie sent me a picture. It's
of a dick. Okay, Jamie Cowboys, but it's because somebody named Jamie's Cowboys,
poor mom. It looks like bloggers. Okay, it's pretty well as a really small penis. So it has
it's probably Aldi, I think. It's so small. It's like, but she thinks it's she thinks it goes. I don't
I think it's ghost. Yeah, it's a small piece. It's a really small
Well ghost ghost is a great big fat person. So why wouldn't he have a little one?
It looks like kind of like because I saw a picture of blogger's butthole again
Like I was in my email when I was going through them
It looks like I like a blow up doll. I mean, it's like it looks like some kind of like rubber piece on his butthole
I don't know what it is. It just looks weird. It looks like it looks like you know the thing like when you blow up a pool float
It looks like that's there
that's not good you know like a like one of those float like the air floaty things like the
you know playable dragon and stuff it looks like one of those little like the thing that pops out
and you pop it back in and stuff that's what looks like it makes me that sounds fucked up
did you let him in yeah he said he's approved
Oh
Yeah, whatever you're describing sounds real fucked up, but I don't want to I don't want to see that I don't even want to imagine
Yeah, I wait to I wait to psyche
The prolapse butthole
Ew, what is it supposed to say?
Prolet, like when it starts coming out,
like that's cool.
Yeah, it looks like it's like,
You know
Come on like you don't know from personal experience like you get out
It looks like a balloon. We thought you'd even fucking prolapse and popped or something. I don't know how to explain
It's just pretty strange. Hey, 50 comments
There's almost 80 people in the chat tonight guys. This is a this is awesome. Okay 80 people in the chat
We're earlier like a few minutes ago. There's 80 people now. There's 50. Well, we really brought in 80. See we're good
guys don't have to power the power of like you know the cff mix with the power of cff the power
chat friendship and then it's like with mixed with the um c op which is the uh cope of psyche
or k op i'm sorry k op and then um it's the power of demonetization i think it is because it's like
that actually like exercises the demon it was like there's like some kind of demon that's like
saying oh my god you're you're gonna worry about that yeah like you had this dark cloud yeah the
It's gonna be a brand now. Yeah, no now those were your outer demons now. You gotta now the only thing stop and use your inner
Um, well you got rid of a few demons. Um, I did, especially let me see. I think that Mason, I think that Mason guy was a high ranking demon of hell. I mean, it's like, he has to be like a banshee. Yeah.
Also, really, our autistic people pretty much are just like, you know, like kings of hell. I figured. Mason's a fake. Like he was faking being autistic.
He was? I keep hearing that. Was that, guys, did you hear that?
Well, you can be pretty convincing at it though. I gotta say pretty fucking
Why am I here? She's like, I don't know why are you here? He's like, uh, psyche told me go over here
And she's like, why didn't you tell you that? And it's like, well, I think he was doing it for a long time
And that's how good he is at it now
What if people do that in this community? It's like it's like it's like as as a common as like macing a homeless person in this community
It's making way where did mason go actually? He's probably at the other channel looking for me. So psyche psyche
Hey psyche. Hey psyche, um
And then it's like then he won't come on camera. I thought you were keeping him around to groom him or something
I know what the fuck was going on
Well, he's a grown man, he's a technically a grown man even if he is slow 40 years old
Yeah, I mean like he's a kid more, you know
He's very cute. He's the Ed Norton of YouTube.
Thing, you have his Star Wars shirt. Yeah, give Mason like a Star Wars shirt, please.
He needs it in his shirt. He can't just keep wearing that blue one forever. I mean, it's like,
it's a nice shirt, but now it's turned like gray in blue instead of white in blue.
And, uh... It's concerning. It is concerning. I'm worried about it. Mason...
Change your shirt, please. Even if it's the same like just get a three pack of that one
I just don't want the exact same shirt. That's like
It's okay, it's your fault. Yeah, I don't think that is what why would you do that to me so now you've embarrassed
Yeah, yeah, it was like Mason do you take Star Wars one night and now all Mason will say is like now
I'd now only talks about a Star Wars because he thinks
You have a Star Wars shirt. He's like, yeah, and then he's like, well, where and he never he never puts it on
So I don't think he really has one
Guys me send me send a pair of drumsticks of paint can and a star wars shirts
It's at the least at the most if you're feeling generous. Let's get him a drum set on T moves for like a hundred bucks
I mean, it's like oh shit. Is that Alex McQueen super cop get your ass up here Alex. Is that beta in her underwear?
I'll be there where that is rain
That's for me
on who work would be that would be there. Trust me. I wouldn't be with rain if that was her.
I've seen his underwear. Actually,
dark shadow, but yeah, I saw something under there. No.
No, God, you said she had a five o'clock shadow. What she dropped the camera once when she was on the show and then
And then she changed her underwear while the camera was on the floor like right under her
But all we see what always I was a dark shadow
Like a few when I was a mug like that. I wouldn't doubt it. I would not doubt it
What happened with you two? I thought you two were so internet-close, you know what happened?
Well, you know what I'm gonna come sit. I got out that the internet's a bunch of bullshit
It is it is I mean people could say they're anybody, you know, that's why I said internet close, right? You caught that so right
I mean, I'm I'm smart, you know, I get it
I get I understand a brand saying I smart to win from the trip kick videos that turns out that's just some AI face
I see everywhere now. I mean, it's like
That's what you know, you know, you've made it when you become a meme. I didn't yeah the Persian Bush
I did it. I did a picture of her and she was like, oh, that's no insulting
It looks better. I mean, you're like, well, fuck, it looks better than the real thing. I didn't want to say that
I was trying to be nice.
Oh, Zondra made a wonderful music video, too, which I'll play right now, and she made B2 look amazing.
And I don't want to, like, you know, start any problem.
You try to make them look better, and they get mad at you for that.
And the thing that is, isn't it mad? Because the thing that is, I know you get mad when I, like, even mention her name,
but you know what? I haven't looked at her show the other day, and she was mentioning my name and say anything.
So I'm going to play.
Sometimes you gotta be the bigger person about it, you know?
Being that is, are you in love with Beaton?
Because look, look, why would you yell at me, and then whatever she says is like, oh,
poor baby Beaton.
And it's like, whatever I say is like, oh, I'm Satan, right?
No, she doesn't landscape, she manscapes.
Kate and Sam are going to war, Carl Fulmigst, oh my gosh, oh yeah, oh there's a picture
Did you know that you're in this video JT? Oh, well, let's let's have a look
I'll show you the picture of it. Hold on one second. I'm in a video. I
Know I just see the picture of you
But you need a picture of me. I have a picture of you
It's just to you. I don't want to ask him. He's gonna verify if this one is you on
Where is this? Where is this? I mean, I could give you a picture. It's no problem a
nude photo
Hello
Okay, no, I don't see the picture anymore.
I mean, there was a picture there,
but I just don't see any more picture.
I can do picture.
It's okay.
Samman versus the, what is the, what's going on here?
Oh, Crystal Marie goes off on good times for life.
Oh my God.
Crystal Marie versus Christine Psyche Mod.
Oh wow.
Okay, well, is that weird picture
where you're like looking in the bushes at somebody?
You remember using that as a profile picture before?
You were like you're like this weird guy like this and he's like looking in the bushes and it remember was like that weird
Oh, maybe it was like I'm Vader was that picture actually. I don't know. I was looking in the bush
There's some guy in the bushes
Looking through the bushes at me. It might have been Vader. Yeah, I don't think I look in bushes and stuff
I don't want to play the video, but I would definitely show you the picture of you play the video.
Am I hiding in a bush like yeah, you are I'll show you I don't remember ever doing that
Remember JT hiding in a bush. I mean, this is you JT pretty sure. I never was hiding in bushes, but
Jesus you don't know what we look like goddamn. I know you over here. Okay, right here look
Okay, now look in the middle like we're my cursor is going the gray hair. Is that you?
Where am I? Where am I? Do you see?
Is it in this picture here? Yeah, do you see right here?
Just see a gravestone. I don't see it. I see a bush
Okay, I'm gonna put this on. I don't see anything
See a gravestone. That's strange. Okay. Yeah, like you have like a
Like an overlay on I think you're
Okay, I'll take it off. Hey watch this one psyche. You're not brand new. I know I'm like I'm acting like I'm all
I'm just brand new to this. Okay. That's unlike your brand new
Yeah, I don't recall ever hiding in a bush.
You're hiding in the bush.
Okay, I promise you.
Okay.
You're going to see it in one second.
I'm going to share this now again.
Okay.
I'm going to share again.
Where is it?
Share.
And.
Entire.
Also the entire screen.
And then look at this right.
Here.
Okay.
Look right here.
I don't I don't see where do you see that person here? You're not showing anything. You're not showing us anything
Why is that showing it like you are you trolling in?
You're a little troll, aren't you? No, okay. Nice. Okay. Watch
Oh that guy
I was hiding in the fucking
No, that was later. No, I remember that day. Yeah, I was like, hi. I was hiding in the in a plant
Yeah, I'm hiding a potted plant
No, you know now that you brought it up, yeah now I remember you got it you got to put the pick on
Okay
Why sing there of course like drinking
Oh god
The blue shirt
Being at that which oh, there's she's Jesus mason
You know who she is, right?
Why is it smiling and look off camera?
She was going to do that to me, you know what I'm saying?
Like, she never started with that.
Listen, buddy, don't ever let Jigard down, especially
with men like that.
She is a man, by the way.
Oh, she is a man, by the way.
OK, outrageous.
Don't say that down.
She's scandalous.
Oh, man, it's OK.
Are you serious, though, or are you just saying
it's like it's probably all that hard?
Really a scandal of our time
We've gone pronouns pronouns now. Okay. She's a pronoun. He she
Have you ever seen that
No
Yeah, this is my case a little harder
A lot of people thought I was this guy
But I don't know some people thought you were this guy named Carl the guy that's the guy on the left
You're nothing like that guy. No, they think we sound the same
You don't even sound the same
Mason stocks a lot of people
Okay, Mary, if you know the channel just posted in the chat
We actually found his like a rest record. No, he does the oblivious return thing really well
The rest records who found that his rest is twice in a church
Yeah, like for trespassing
Yeah, well, what the hell was he doing trespassing in a church you wouldn't leave us passing. Yeah, but what was he trying to do in there?
It's kind of odd. You're gonna pray on women
In church look at that
Hey, like this jc where it's where's that? Who's that 30 diamonds? That's that's 40 diamond. Huh?
What do you think? I wasn't gonna say I thought you were gay psyche
I am technically that the fucking man. So
Yeah, it's gonna say the tits look too real to be fucking diamond
Yeah, pretty diamonds boobs look like melted Hershey's kisses. They look yeah
That's a nice way to put it. Yeah. Oh my gosh, but I mean Hershey's kisses are sweet
Even when they melt it up
Not as good as good when they're melted. They're like melted and then re-re
You put them back in the fridge. Oh, I put them in the freezer. Oh, I love it. Yeah
You just like chew them all hard. Oh
Hey, Perry pagey, that's pretty pagey. That is pagey. Oh, that is page. I did the glamour shot of look at this glamour shot
She's using
Halloween
No, that was a viral costume. What is this?
She's like a van. I think she was a mermaid. I think
Diamond she gets shoulder-catchers like a linebacker. No, this was my outfit. I went
I mean, I'm sure. No, this this was my outfit. I went as crusty the clown. Oh
My god, you went into the Jewish clown. Yeah
That's that's Sam man's photo. No
Is it? No, it's Christy the clown when he takes his makeup off
Christy the clown
Yes
Yeah, he's a Jewish. I'm not a huge Simpsons fan, but I do know what that character looks like
I mean that was like, you know the height of the Simpsons life. I think I nailed it
Oh, it's an everyday selfie. I don't page. You're all like, you know, it looks like you're wearing black lipstick
Are you got in that photo?
Have you met Ziggy page? You might want to meet this guy. He's he's he's a he looks like good charlotte's
Apparently Paige goes way back with Ziggy. She does. Is he Canadian?
Hopefully not too far back. He knows each other for some reason. They're like Ziggy's not Canadian
But they've known each other for a while now. That is weird. That's so weird. Well, how would she know?
Page, what are you not telling me? I don't know. He said I he met her like somewhere
The church of Satan no congregation. I mean, it's like, you know, what else does he do? I mean, it's like I'm guessing like had another stream
I don't know
You're on the stream page you're cheating easy didn't go into details. Well, that means there's something suspicious going on
You met Zingy and Jan? Oh, yeah, Zingy. She met Zingy. Oh, that's not too far back then is it? Yeah, Zingy and Jan
Oh, it almost sounds like the Baronstein Bears authors remember you used to be like Stan and Jan Baronstein
but now it's like Zingy. Baronstein, what do you think about that the whole Baronstein, Baronstein?
What do you think about the whole Mandela effect? I think the Mandela effect is
bullshit, but
I mean, it works because there's, because there's things that are like saturized and the satire becomes more popular than the actual thing, like, like, Luke, I am your father.
And then it's like at the original movies, like, do you remember it as baron stain?
I remember Bernstein Bears.
And it's like, but it was probably Stein and probably spelled Stein.
We just had stain.
No, it's like, because it wasn't like, so we weren't sort of the Jewish aware back.
Like it was spelled with an E.
I don't know I don't I don't think it was I think I was always with an A
Do you remember do you remember Froot of the loom having a cornucopia?
Listen when people start talking about shit like that. It just makes them sound nuts
But I raised him with a cornucopia. They're kind of shaped like I don't know
I don't know. Maybe they're what I don't know. I just ask how people remember it
Mandela dying in the 80s in prison or in the
I wasn't alive in the 80s. So I don't know. Oh my god. Me either. Oh my god
You're too young to me talking to my let me talking to you guys. You're over 18, right? Well, we're over 21. Yeah
Well, I don't know. That's where they got it. They said he died or something, but then he was actually alive. Yeah
Exactly, but they said he died in prison, but I think there are rumors that he died in prison or something during that time
If you're like, you know, such a popular political figure
And so I thought he was in prison in the first place, but I don't know. I don't know. I don't know what I don't know what
It's just weird people. Do you remember it that way psyche? No, I remember because I was like in high school
We had like a
we were like studying South Africa and apartheid it was like 1999 was when the apartheid was like
overturned that's because they had this kind of caste system in South Africa and so they had a
ballot and Nelson Mandela was like on the ballot and it was like a huge ballot it was all like
pictures of people because some people were illiterate and it was a big ballot and it's like
and he won like by a landslide and so that's I never heard of him dying at all but then the Mandela
which is like a sacred geometry kind of thing in Hinduism that he's designer things like these
like kind of like patterns and stuff like all in a circle and that's a mandala and that kind of
is along the lines of maybe that's where they got that from yeah I hear I be heard I even say
they thought he died till he came to you didn't hear anything until he died from the internet
yeah I don't know I don't know maybe in some places they were recording that maybe
The world is a stage and we are about players in the stage.
Yeah, do you think that everything's fake?
I think a lot of things that are presented to us are fake.
A lot at the end that we also take part in a lot of fake things
just because it's like culture.
Yeah, I think the same way.
But uh, like the world is especially America America is like built on the grip. It really is it's like very like
Everything is a scam in America everything everything. It's like from tow truck companies to the
Tricky like McDonald's
McDonald's monopoly game to I mean everything is like
you know i want a lot of free food with those actually oh my god i have free mcdonald's
rest of the month but that expires november or something i mean it's like but nobody's gonna
win a million dollars from mcdonald's i know somebody we know a family when i was a kid we
know a family in our city and they're friends of ours and they won the million dollars in mcdonald's
game and they bought a house and everything but the mcdonald's game was rigged in the 90s through
like the 2000s by like this guy that owned the
printing company, and he would steal the game pieces at one and he'd, I'm afraid to remember
his mom. No, I want shaking nuggets.
I don't want chicken nuggets. I don't like chicken nuggets either, and you know, you know what? There's more chicken nuggets sold
There are even chickens in the world
Well, yeah, cuz they're a little tiny things, you know
Well, why don't we why don't we eat chicks?
Have you ever thought about that wouldn't they be like kind of like the veal of the poultry at front?
I don't know if there'd be a lot of meat on it. You know, it's like a little baby
It's just like a veal calf is it have a lot of meat on they beat it with milk and it's all fat. Yeah, you know cows like
Even a baby calf is like still bigger than a little chick. I don't know like a little chick
I ordered veal one time at a restaurant and my mom good look and I had to not order it
She was very against me like it. I didn't need it
I had to stop I had to cancel the order on it because she's she's like that's like she's like that's a baby cow
Do you know it's good like really good?
felt bad
Are you vegan? No, I wasn't vegetarian for two years, but I'm not a vegan.
You've seen this guy eat McDonald's like
Yeah, I forgot about the fish tacos. Yeah
McDonald's vegan psyche McDonald's has page loves deal. Oh my god
Well paid page ones eight like, you know half of life moose, so I'm not surprised. No
Page has like pages like a moose head that she she slaughtered herself and she you know
Cut off all the meat herself and I don't know if I was going to peg anybody for being vegan
It would be page no offense page, but it's called boo-winkle, huh page. I'm sorry. No, I just didn't you know
I've never eaten moose. What does that taste like?
What
Roast what does moose tastes like I've never eaten
What does a moose tastes like I heard it tastes like a bore no, I don't know it tastes maybe like a
Camel I don't know what does a moose tastes like
People eat camels
They're very fatty those humps are all all fat, you know, they're not water like people say they're fat
Oh Alexander wants to link
Well, then I'm not gonna post. I'm just kidding. No, come on Alexander get up here. He wants to bullshit with us, right?
Rami is filled with parasites probably right get on up here Alex gear get your cop ass up here
No, no, no, no, no end tower. No enter. You know, like the only meats I eat are chicken and beef. I don't eat pork at all
Well pork that mean that's like a Jewish diet or Muslim is they don't they don't and I don't eat fish either
Well, I do like certain fish. I don't like it. Yeah, it can't smell like fish though
Good fresh fish with like a lot of lemon on it. Oh, yeah, like lemon butter capers. Oh, like
Like, you know a nice like a yes to be it has to be like
That's not like a delicate taste. It cannot taste strong a fishy. I hunt a fish and we have a red and black angus cattle farm
I'm the furthest from vegan. Yeah, Paige slaughters her own cows
I mean it's like she like she literally like comes with it like a this like taser
Electroshocks the cow and then slices neck and it's like serves it for dinner. That's like this is
Wild thing like where they were slicing the neck I call it wild things a movie with the
No, no, no, no, like where they kill the halal like the oh, yeah, you're talking about the muslim
Yeah, like they slice its neck like yeah. Well, yeah, because you have to bless it and like the blood drain out of it, right?
Yeah, it sounds like when when ziki, you know, like kills his chickens to prepare the meat
Doesn't this he does he kill his chickens and satanic sacrifices. I just have to know
I don't know he he's never clear with that with us
Then he's doing that if he's not being clear about it. No, I don't think he's into the occult aspect of it
It's more like the philosophy. He has the freaking goatia as his profile. I know he does boy
And he has the tattoos
He was in a band now and they all had it
Edgy it sounds like he like he's a devotee of ipos though
Like JT like JT said it's more of his philosophy
You know, I was a philosophical Satanist when I was a teenager, but it's like I grew out of because it was so like evil
I mean, it's like they really they look at people like cattle. They want to like
People in a zoo basically. Yeah, that's Ziggie. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Ziggie
Grow up Ziggie. I mean, it's like that's funny when you're like 13 years old and you believe that but it's like eventually
You grow a heart. I know and he's 40 years old. Oh my god
He's not he's not that bad
Well, I think he's bad
He sounds a little bit evil to me. I heard and he was on some show like I think Tommy James's show and being evil
Ziggy does be evil sometimes
Yeah, but who isn't sometimes, you know, well
Lots of good questions. I don't think I'm not evil. I mean, I'm not evil to people but it's like, you know, maybe I'm a little bit like
Ali I have an alien emotion sometimes why tell us JT and Aztec are siblings. We got the clips
I don't believe that they are that'd be very straight. I've said can I see them kiss and I'd be like incest
We're not brother and sister JT doesn't have any sisters
Hello
Alex McQueen Alex so whatever clips you have like bring it bitch
I would you have them being born at the hospital man, cuz whatever you have is bullshit
I'm the villain of the sector. What are you? Oh my god? I'm doing already
Why am I so yeah? I'm like such a nice. I'm like actually really one of the nicest good-hearted people in the sector
Yeah, a little too nice a little too nice my man. That's the problem
A little bit too being Alex
The people over on top of your head this freak out these two losers are the ones that poor mom you take and took your panel down
And now they're sitting here with you manipulating you
That's crazy
No one no one person took my panel my channel that was it was it was a collective effort
I think it was a group effort. You know what and they give me a favor. So fuck you guys. No, everything's better now
I think you guys everything is better. I'm gonna I'm actually
This is like a blessing in disguise
Pretty cool, right? I cried. It's pretty cool JT has been bad. Those they took your panel down these two little freaks
That's fucked up, bro. Alex is always blaming
And kid these two losers
He's always blaming us for his fucking I don't know. He's fucking demented or something
I'm talking to Alex backstage. This is all an act. It's just a joke. Oh
It is no his whole stick that this what he's doing now. It's all character
Yeah, so you have same man as your avatar you doxing loser shut the fuck up
These two took you down
Shut the fuck up bitch
She's a hooker from hell. Yeah. Yeah, exactly. And now they're here alone because right they took your shit down
Not a lot here because oh it's all gone. So they try to take over again. Dude. It's you
You're such a loser
Transparent though be better at what you do
Don't be so transparent because the whole world sees it
Alex Alex Alex
How's your daughter, bro?
Oh, that's right. You never see her anymore. Do you?
damn
That sounds just like Ziggy
Actually, that's where just like spunky and just in that's pumped and just in Boyle you fucking losers
It's like you wake up and take this fucking free
No, I actually wanted to know how she doing
Spunky she's good. Well, she's still with that jerk Justin Boyle, but
No, I meant I meant Alex's daughter. Oh
I don't think I think it's a he doesn't know either
You're like you're asking the wrong guy, did you do the Ziggy thing and sign her away to I
Don't know let's not make it about Ziggy though. I don't know right here. Oh
Okay, my bad
Do I have permission to crash out?
Yes
Look at these losers. What's going on Alex? Where you been, man?
You suck my dick thought it's your big dream. Oh shit. He turned him down to well nice, but he's been reduced to background
Yeah, let's just let him keep yelling like a lunatic
What you gonna talk over me now so you're crazy you don't let people talk okay, I talk
Well, at least we're not crazy enough to talk to ourselves. That's a good thing. Shut up, bitch. Shut the fuck down. Bow down to me, suck my dick. Bow down to McQueen.
So anyways, I thought Gotti was gonna show up.
Why'd you think that?
I don't know. He said he was gonna come by. Well, he didn't say specifically when.
Nah, Gotti is doing his thing, man. I was with Gotti early. He's good.
I kicked him off a panel earlier. I paid money, I got him kicked.
He's around. Don't worry about Gotti.
You don't worry about Gotti. Gotti's in our discord. You don't worry about him.
Shut the fuck up, you stupid bitch!
You don't worry about him.
You fucking losers! Shut the fuck up, both of you!
Worthless bums. Worthless bums.
Yeah, he's faggot now. He's just jealous.
It's just it's just troll thing man
It's a jealousy thing. No, it's it's a character. He's playing a fucking care
I've literally talked to this guy backstage nothing like this. When did you talk to him backstage?
Fuck if I remember, but I've spoken to him backstage
We had a normal conversation believe it or not
Huh
Recently
No, no, no recently I haven't been here fucking really how many it's been months since I've been on panels. Oh
No, but I talked to the guy you could even say he's fucking maybe semi-normal I don't fucking know
Don't think so. Yeah, it's the character people get up here. They want to play a fucking character
Am I interrupting should I leave
And the story
I run CFF now you heard
Okay Alex you run CFF, okay
Okay, buddy, okay little bro you wanna you wanna ice cream I can go get you an ice cream
Yeah, he fagged out crashed out
He's honestly, he's still not as bad as goes
No, I mean they're both pretty bad
Shut up bitch drop a dollar to say
Five cents your book losers shut the fuck up and get out of office panel unless you don't need it
But you're not even members
Yeah, all you do is go on panels and talk shit drop a dollar. Well, you're not gonna get an ice cream with that attitude. I
Was gonna take you to McDonald's but now I'm not going to
Jamie I didn't watch the alien earth. I heard it was good. I heard the ending kind of dropped off
I don't know
There's the video losers. See how they dance together when they're broken. I just broke them together
Two birds for the price of one
Giggling please make Donald's jokes. Shut the fuck up and drop a dollar a super cop. Okay
Yo, why don't you super chat a dollar? Oh, I know why cuz you can't you can't afford a dollar
So your little girl is gonna laugh. He he he what a nice tactic you guys go in here
You
You ain't asked a glory or nothing
And this guy's a doxin loser. Let's say a man as his avatar talk about losers
No, by the way, the Dodgers one the Dodgers one you heard for you can eat you faggots fuck you in Toronto the Dodgers win
Fuck you
Five cents
You have a quarter to spend
Yeah, this is boring
I much more prefer to talk to psyche
No, dude, psyche left us here for a reason. Yeah, psyche's gone, baby. You got me now
You know that that was so hilarious when you would do that
You would just leave the panel
That's crazy and asked a warrior to hook a little loser bitch and beat a boy
The life depended on it your CFS sucks my dick. I run CFS now
Look at us now. We're not even we're barely even doing anything
No, man, if you took the energy that you you spent on this on your daughter, you might have a relationship with her, right?
Well, maybe it's better that you don't I don't know
You notice whenever it gets real like she gets really quiet
I'm sorry. We're staying character. I got me fucked up
You want to go rain
Yeah, this is boring. Yeah, I mean let him fag up by himself. Yeah
of night. Golden wings glowed in the candlelight. Crowds came running just to see the flame,
but envy was the price of fame. And now he stands where the echoes fall, with tarot in
hand hearing every call. From praise to venom, in the same breath said, but the fire in his